<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/</link><description>Chloe's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 09:25:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Take Physical Products Global?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-take-physical-products-global/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 09:25:20 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-take-physical-products-global/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Blindly pouring money into ads or simply shipping your product overseas often leads to overstock and costly trial-and-error.
Successful global expansion starts by answering three strategic questions: <strong>Why go global? Where to go? And how to sell efficiently?</strong></p>
<h2 id="strategic-preparation">Strategic Preparation</h2>
<h3 id="1-define-the-goal-of-going-global">1. Define the Goal of Going Global</h3>
<p>Going global is not a trend to follow — it’s a <strong>strategic decision</strong> based on your company’s growth stage and external pressures.
Before taking any operational steps, companies must <strong>define and quantify</strong> their globalization objectives. These typically fall into three main categories:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Allocate Online Advertising Budget</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-allocate-online-advertising-budget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:50:07 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-allocate-online-advertising-budget/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>As the person in charge of online advertising for a market, facing the new quarterly KPI targets and advertising budget from your company, you need to ask yourself the following questions:</p>
<ul>
<li>What is the main focus of this quarter’s KPIs? Is it <strong>scaling up</strong>, <strong>improving efficiency</strong>, or <strong>increasing customer value</strong>?</li>
<li>Compared with the previous quarter, what are the main changes in KPIs and market conditions? Which channels are facing a sharp increase in customer acquisition cost (CAC)?</li>
<li>Do you think the KPI target is <strong>achievable with the current budget</strong>? Is the growth logic behind it reasonable?</li>
<li>If you believe there’s a significant gap between targets and resources, how will you use <strong>historical ROI data</strong> to negotiate with leadership for more reasonable goals or resources? (Of course, in most cases, you’ll still have to get it done with limited resources 😉)</li>
<li>Once the <strong>final KPIs</strong> are confirmed, how will you allocate this quarter’s ad budget to ensure the KPIs are met?</li>
</ul>
<p>This article uses “improving customer quality” as an example to share a practical framework for ad budget allocation.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Everyday Review: Natural Language-Driven Cross-App Automation</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/everyday-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 07:42:18 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/everyday-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong><a href="https://www.everyday.new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Everyday</a></strong> is a personal AI assistant designed to help users complete tasks and multi-step workflows across different applications through simple natural language commands. It aims to boost productivity and allow users to focus on what truly matters.</p>
<p>In short, Everyday is an “all-in-one AI” that turns user intentions into real outcomes—helping you clean up your inbox, organize daily work, and drive progress, so you can focus on higher-value tasks.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Dreamflow Review: AI Mobile App Builder</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/dreamflow-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:26:19 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/dreamflow-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://dreamflow.app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">DreamFlow</a> is an <strong>AI mobile app builder</strong> designed to make the app development process <strong>automated</strong>, <strong>visual</strong>, and <strong>code-based</strong>. Its goal is to let users create <strong>production-ready applications</strong> faster than ever — combining the <strong>speed of AI</strong> for rapid prototyping and iteration with <strong>full control over the underlying code</strong>, ensuring that the final output is high-quality, scalable, and commercially viable.</p>
<p>How users build with Dreamflow:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><strong>Describe your app</strong>
Use natural language to tell the system what you want to build.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Profound Review: The Enterprise-Grade Generative Engine Optimization (GEO) Platform in the AI Era</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/profound-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:24:13 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/profound-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong><a href="https://www.tryprofound.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Profound</a></strong> is a <strong>GEO (Generative Engine Optimization)</strong> tool built for <strong>enterprise brands and marketers</strong>, designed to help brands <strong>monitor and optimize their visibility</strong> within AI-driven search and chat environments such as <strong>ChatGPT, Google AI Overviews, and Perplexity</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="product-slogan">Product Slogan</h2>
<p></p>
<p>On the homepage, <strong>Profound</strong> highlights its core value through a dynamic slogan:</p>
<p>“Get your brand mentioned by” — followed by a rotating list of AI chat tools and icons like <strong>ChatGPT, Perplexity, and Claude</strong>.<br>
This slogan clearly conveys Profound’s core mission: to <strong>help brands appear in AI-generated answers</strong>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>AI Glossary for Beginners</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-glossary-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:35:34 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-glossary-for-beginners/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Have you noticed that <strong>AI (Artificial Intelligence)</strong> seems to be everywhere these days? It’s embedded in the tools and products we use every day. However, once discussions dive into the technical side—terms like <strong>Agent</strong>, <strong>Knowledge Base</strong>, and <strong>MCP</strong>—things can get confusing.</p>
<p><strong>This article is for you—the AI beginner.</strong> My goal is to help you build a clear and reliable understanding of essential AI terminology. I’ll explain each concept in <strong>simple, straightforward language</strong> so you can grasp their real-world functions.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to SEM Data Analysis</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-analytics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:12:39 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-analytics/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-sem-analysis">What is SEM Analysis?</h2>
<p></p>
<p>In the battleground of Search Engine Marketing (SEM), running ads is only half the battle. What truly sets you apart and even helps you surpass competitors is <strong>SEM analysis</strong>. It acts as the &ldquo;eyes&rdquo; and &ldquo;brain&rdquo; of your ad strategy, helping you understand what happened, why it happened, and what you should do next.</p>
<p>Simply put, <strong>SEM analysis is the systematic process of collecting, measuring, analyzing, and reporting data related to search engine marketing.</strong> This data includes, but is not limited to: how many times your ads were seen (<strong>impressions</strong>), how many times they were clicked (<strong>clicks</strong>), how many conversions they generated (<strong>conversions</strong>), and how much you paid for them (<strong>ad spend</strong>). By digging deep into this data, you can comprehensively evaluate ad campaign performance, identify potential optimization opportunities, and provide solid data support for future marketing strategies.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to SEM Bidding Strategies</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-bidding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:04:45 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-bidding/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-sem-bidding">What is SEM Bidding?</h2>
<p>Imagine you&rsquo;re in a bustling digital marketplace, eager to sell your products or services. Customers are looking for specific items, and both you and your competitors want to display your offerings in the most prominent spots. In this market, whoever gets seen first captures the opportunity. In the world of Search Engine Marketing (SEM), this process of &ldquo;contesting for prominent positions&rdquo; is called <strong>SEM Bidding</strong>.</p>
<p>Simply put, <strong>SEM bidding refers to the process where advertisers set bids for specific keywords on search engine advertising platforms (like Google Ads, Microsoft Ads) to compete for ad display positions and clicks.</strong> Your bid, along with other factors like ad quality, collectively determines whether your ad appears at the top when a user searches, or if it doesn&rsquo;t appear at all.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to Landing Page Optimization</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/landing-page-optimization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:34:36 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/landing-page-optimization/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="whats-a-landing-page">What&rsquo;s a Landing Page?</h2>
<p>When you meticulously plan and launch an SEM ad, successfully attracting user clicks—<strong>where do they go next?</strong> They don&rsquo;t randomly jump to just any page, nor do they land on your website&rsquo;s &ldquo;About Us&rdquo; or blog posts. Instead, they&rsquo;re directed to a carefully considered, specially designed digital &ldquo;gateway&rdquo;—a <strong>landing page</strong>.</p>
<p>Put simply, <strong>a landing page is a web page created specifically for a particular marketing or advertising campaign. Its sole purpose is to guide visitors to complete a specific action (i.e., a &ldquo;conversion&rdquo;)</strong>. This action could be signing up for a newsletter, downloading an e-book, requesting a free trial, purchasing a product, or filling out a contact form, among others.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>What is SEM? A Beginner's Guide</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-basics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:23:48 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-basics/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-sem">What is SEM?</h2>
<p>If you&rsquo;ve ever searched on search engines like Google or Bing, you&rsquo;ve definitely seen links with <strong>&ldquo;Ad&rdquo;</strong> or <strong>&ldquo;Sponsored&rdquo;</strong> labels appearing above the organic results. These paid advertisements are the core of <strong>Search Engine Marketing (SEM)</strong>.</p>
<p>Simply put, SEM is a digital marketing strategy that gains traffic and visibility on search engine results pages (SERPs) through <strong>paid methods</strong>. Its ultimate goal is to increase your website&rsquo;s exposure on search engines, thereby attracting more potential customers.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>