<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/</link><description>Chloe's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:58:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basic Concepts of Commercialization</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-concepts-of-commercialization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:58:46 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-concepts-of-commercialization/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-commercialization">What is Commercialization?</h2>
<p>When people hear “commercialization,” the first thought is often “making money.” That’s not wrong—turning a business, product, or traffic into revenue is indeed the core goal. However, commercialization can be understood in <strong>two perspectives: narrow and broad</strong>.</p>
<h3 id="narrow-perspective-result-oriented-ways-to-make-money">Narrow Perspective: Result-Oriented Ways to Make Money</h3>
<p>From the most direct angle, commercialization is about converting your business directly into revenue. Some simple examples include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Product Sales</strong>: Selling goods or services directly generates income, e.g., e-commerce selling clothing or online platforms selling courses.</li>
<li><strong>Advertising Monetization</strong>: Earning revenue from traffic, e.g., social media or short-video platforms displaying ads while users browse content.</li>
<li><strong>Membership Fees</strong>: Users pay for a better experience or exclusive content, e.g., premium subscriptions.</li>
</ul>
<p>This perspective is obvious: it focuses on <strong>“how to make money”</strong>, emphasizing results. The key question is how your business generates revenue from users and how to maximize short-term returns.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Make Integrated Marketing Strategy</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-make-integrated-marketing-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:57:49 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-make-integrated-marketing-strategy/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="1-user-insights-and-journey-analysis">1. User Insights and Journey Analysis</h2>
<p>Before formulating any integrated marketing strategy, in-depth user insights and journey analysis are indispensable foundational work. They help the brand truly understand who the target users are, their needs and pain points, as well as their behavior patterns along the purchase path, thus providing a scientific basis for subsequent strategy formulation.</p>
<h3 id="what-is-user-insight">What is User Insight?</h3>
<p>User insight is a deep understanding of the target users, covering their basic profiles (age, gender, region, occupation, etc.), behavior habits, interests and preferences, purchasing motivations, and barriers. It is obtained through data analysis (website behavior data, social interaction data, CRM data, etc.), user interviews, surveys, and market research, providing a comprehensive and multidimensional user perspective.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>A Practical Guide to Efficiently Managing Images in Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:31:21 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When taking notes in Obsidian, using images is almost inevitable. Copying and pasting images directly is indeed convenient, but over time you&rsquo;ll find that the images are chaotically placed, resizing them is troublesome, and centering an image is even more difficult. Another pitfall is that when you delete an image from a note, the file doesn’t actually disappear but remains hidden in the root directory.</p>
<h2 id="what-exactly-are-images-in-obsidian">What Exactly Are Images in Obsidian?</h2>
<p>When it comes to images, many people’s first thought is that &ldquo;inserting an image means adding an image directly.&rdquo; However, in Obsidian, images are more like references to &ldquo;external files.&rdquo; In other words, the images aren’t directly embedded in the note content but are stored in folders on your computer and then displayed in the notes through links or references.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Complete Guide to Installing and Getting Started with Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:13:58 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In the era of information overload, more and more people are realizing that organizing and consolidating knowledge is more important than acquiring it. <a href="https://obsidian.md/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Obsidian</a>, a note-taking app focused on <strong>local knowledge management</strong>, has rapidly gained popularity among productivity enthusiasts and knowledge workers in recent years. It is not just another cloud-based note-taking tool but a &ldquo;second brain&rdquo; system that emphasizes <strong>local storage, Markdown formatting, and linked thinking</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="the-core-philosophy-of-obsidian">The Core Philosophy of Obsidian</h2>
<p>At its core, Obsidian is about building a knowledge network that you control. Unlike traditional linear note-taking, Obsidian advocates for <strong>nonlinear linked notes</strong>. By linking different notes, you can create a multidimensional, interconnected knowledge graph.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How Can SEO and SEM Collaborate to Adapt to AI Max for Search?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:08:54 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>With generative AI fully penetrating the advertising space, Google&rsquo;s <a href="https://blog.google/products/ads-commerce/google-ai-max-for-search-campaigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max for Search</a> is transforming how search marketing operates. Similar automated ad products have also emerged on platforms like Meta and TikTok.</p>
<p>Compared to the traditional keyword-centric approach, AI Max for Search relies more on comprehensive learning from user behavior signals, historical conversion data, and creative assets, with AI autonomously deciding when, to whom, and in what combination to display ads. Simply put, manual control is giving way to &ldquo;signal feeding&rdquo; and &ldquo;model learning.&rdquo;</p>]]></description></item><item><title>When to Use Performance Max vs. Demand Gen?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:36:25 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="whats-the-difference-between-performance-max-and-demand-gen-campaigns">What’s the Difference Between Performance Max and Demand Gen Campaigns?</h2>
<p><strong>Performance Max (PMax)</strong> is a fully automated campaign type by Google that allows advertisers to run a single campaign across all Google-owned channels—Search, Display, YouTube, Gmail, Discover, Maps, and more. It serves as a <strong>complement to Search Ads</strong>, helping advertisers reach more potential customers across multiple touchpoints.</p>
<p><strong>Demand Gen Campaigns</strong>, on the other hand, are designed for visually engaging platforms like YouTube and Google Discover. They focus on <strong>sparking interest and creating demand</strong> through short-form videos and in-feed content—ideal for attracting new audiences to your brand or products.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Do Tariffs Affect PPC Advertising?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 09:39:55 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>The answer is definitely: Yes.</strong></p>
<p>When new tariffs are imposed or existing ones are expanded, the <strong>fundamental cost structure of goods</strong> changes, and companies&rsquo; bidding behaviors also shift:</p>
<ul>
<li>Some companies will increase their bids to secure the best ad positions, hoping to maintain existing profits.</li>
<li>Some companies will maintain their current bid levels in the short term, but ad spend may still rise (influenced by other advertisers increasing their bids, leading to an overall industry CPC increase). In the short term, they&rsquo;ll choose to absorb costs to maintain market share.</li>
<li>Other companies will choose to exit this new round of competition, shifting their marketing budgets to other channels.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="what-are-tariffs">What are Tariffs?</h2>
<p>A tariff (Customs Duty) is a mandatory tax levied by a sovereign nation or economic entity on <strong>imported goods</strong> as they cross its customs border. It&rsquo;s one of the most common forms of trade barriers in international trade, enforced and collected by customs agencies.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>FounderPal Review: AI Marketing Tool Hands-On Experience</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/founderpal-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 11:59:03 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/founderpal-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://founderpal.ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">FounderPal</a> is an AI-powered marketing platform, somewhat similar to <a href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Swiftbrief</a>, which we previously reviewed. Its core features include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>AI Marketing Strategy Generator</strong>: Users only need to input basic business details, and the AI will generate a comprehensive marketing strategy within minutes.</li>
<li><strong>User Persona Generator</strong>: Helps users identify and analyze target audiences by creating detailed ideal customer profiles.</li>
<li><strong>Marketing Idea Generator</strong>: Assists users in brainstorming innovative marketing concepts based on industry trends and business objectives.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="website-strategy">Website Strategy</h2>
<h3 id="hero-section-messaging">Hero Section Messaging</h3>
<p></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Hands-On with Swiftbrief: How AI Simplifies SEO Content Creation</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:13:54 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.swiftbrief.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Swiftbrief</a> is an AI-powered SEO platform designed to streamline the content creation process. Its core features include:</p>
<ol>
<li>Automatically generating content outlines based on keyword and topic analysis</li>
<li>Keyword research and clustering</li>
<li>Integrating SEO data to improve content quality and performance</li>
</ol>
<h2 id="test-walkthrough">Test Walkthrough</h2>
<h3 id="sign-up--onboarding">Sign-Up &amp; Onboarding</h3>
<p>During registration, one minor inconvenience is the requirement to enter your website URL—it&rsquo;s a mandatory field:
</p>
<p>Interestingly, the platform experiments with different onboarding methods, letting users choose their preferred learning style during sign-up:
</p>]]></description></item><item><title>What Are the Advantages of Bing Shopping Ads?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/bing-shopping-ads/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 08:49:10 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/bing-shopping-ads/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="bings-market-share-continues-to-grow">Bing&rsquo;s Market Share Continues to Grow</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://gs.statcounter.com/search-engine-market-share" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">StatCounter (2024 data)</a>, Bing holds approximately <strong>3.42%</strong> of the global search engine market share, making it the second-largest search engine after Google.<br>
In the U.S. market, Bing&rsquo;s search engine market share stands at <strong>7.85%</strong>, showing slight growth from 5.97% in 2021. In 2014, Bing reached its peak U.S. market share at <strong>9.9%</strong>.<br>
</p>
<h2 id="why-focus-on-bing-ads">Why Focus on Bing Ads?</h2>
<h3 id="high-purchasing-power-user-base">High-Purchasing-Power User Base</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Significant Male Demographic</strong>: Data from <a href="https://www.similarweb.com/website/bing.com/#demographics" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">SimilarWeb</a> shows that two-thirds (64.15%) of Bing users are male, with over 50% under age 34 (30.7% aged 25-34, 22.17% aged 18-20).</li>
<li><strong>Affluent User Profile</strong>: As reported by <a href="https://coalitiontechnologies.com/blog/bing-statistics-search-and-usage-data-in-2024" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Coalition</a>, 38% of Bing users have a household income exceeding $100,000 annually.</li>
<li><strong>E-Commerce Impact</strong>: Bing Shopping Ads achieve a <strong>43% higher click-through rate (CTR)</strong> compared to Google, driven by partnerships with platforms like Amazon, OfferUp, and Gumtree.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="cross-platform-reach">Cross-Platform Reach</h3>
<p>Bing Ads are displayed across multiple Microsoft-owned platforms:<br>
<strong>1. Yahoo &amp; AOL</strong></p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>