<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/</link><description>Chloe's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Trade-off Between Customer Acquisition Cost and User Quality: How to Achieve High-Quality Growth?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/relationship-between-customer-acquisition-cost-and-user-quality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:35 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/relationship-between-customer-acquisition-cost-and-user-quality/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In today’s digital marketing environment, growth teams face a common challenge: <strong>the imbalance between acquisition scale and acquisition efficiency</strong>.</p>
<p>In the past, many teams treated lowering Customer Acquisition Cost (CAC) as a core KPI. When traffic supply was relatively abundant, this price-driven strategy did enable rapid user growth. However, as market competition intensified, the drawbacks of pursuing low-cost acquisition alone began to surface.</p>
<p>In practice, a reduction in front-end acquisition costs does not always translate into improved back-end returns. A common scenario is that users acquired through low-cost channels or aggressive promotions may lower the average CAC, but significantly underperform in key metrics such as retention and engagement. Without effective control over user quality, low-cost traffic often results in nothing more than meaningless installs, contributing little real value to the business.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Todoist Website Review</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/todoist-website-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:37:57 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/todoist-website-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="core-positioning"><strong>Core Positioning</strong></h2>
<p></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Main headline (Clarity, finally.):</strong> Todoist does not list features in the first sentence (e.g., “the most powerful task manager”). Instead, it directly delivers a <strong>final result</strong>. For people overwhelmed by tasks, “clarity” is an extremely tempting psychological relief.</li>
<li><strong>Subheadline (Join 50+ million professionals who simplify work and life with the world’s #1 to-do list app.):</strong> Mentioning “50 million professionals” and “#1 worldwide” is meant to eliminate trust barriers for new users in the shortest time possible. This use of <strong>social conformity psychology</strong> is far more persuasive than self-promotion.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>On your product landing page, the headline should convey <em>value</em>, and the subheadline should provide <em>evidence</em>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>New Thoughts on SEO</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/new-thoughts-on-seo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:32:24 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/new-thoughts-on-seo/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="research-phase-of-content-creation">Research Phase of Content Creation</h2>
<p>Before you begin writing, you must complete your research. This phase helps you determine your article’s potential impact and prevents you from wasting time on content with no ranking opportunity.</p>
<h3 id="1-interpreting-search-intent">1. Interpreting Search Intent</h3>
<p>Search intent determines whether you can rank.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Evaluate ranking potential:</strong> Look at the SERP. If the top results are all product pages, the keyword has strong transactional intent—no matter how good your informational article is, it will struggle to rank.</li>
<li><strong>Identify true competitors:</strong> Compare only with websites that share the same content purpose. If you’re writing a professional guide but the top results include short Quora answers, ignore those and analyze other high-quality guides.</li>
<li><strong>Build trust:</strong> The fastest way to establish authority is to meet the user’s exact needs. Give users exactly what they came for, not what you think is good for them.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>e.g. Before writing, search your target keyword. If the top 10 results are all videos, consider producing a video instead of an article.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read Nvidia's Financial Statements?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-nvidia-financial-statements/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 09:11:29 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-nvidia-financial-statements/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>For any beginner who wants to gain a deeper understanding of investing, financial statements are a core tool that must be mastered. Financial statements are the quantitative record of a company’s operating activities; they disclose its profitability, asset structure, and cash flows.</p>
<p>This article focuses on the third-quarter report released in 2025 by the world’s leading AI and semiconductor company—<strong>NVIDIA</strong>—as the case study for analysis.</p>
<p>I will cover:</p>
<ol>
<li>The three main financial statements.</li>
<li>Key figures in NVIDIA’s report.</li>
<li>How to use these figures to assess the company’s financial performance and the quality of its growth.</li>
</ol>
<p>First, you need to download NVIDIA’s third-quarter financial report from the company’s official website:
<a href="https://investor.nvidia.com/financial-info/financial-reports/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">https://investor.nvidia.com/financial-info/financial-reports/</a></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Stocks and Bonds</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/stocks-and-bonds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:16:19 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/stocks-and-bonds/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>You may have heard that the key to successful investing lies in “picking the right stocks” or “catching the next big trend.” In reality, however, there is a more fundamental and more powerful determinant in the financial world: <strong>how you allocate your capital</strong>.</p>
<p>Put simply, the majority of variation in investment returns does not depend on whether you bought Alibaba or Tencent. Instead, it depends on which <strong>asset class</strong> you choose to allocate your money to—high-risk, high-return <strong>stocks</strong>, lower-risk <strong>bonds</strong> that provide stable income, or simply holding cash.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Manage Stock Portfolio?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-manage-stock-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 07:12:23 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-manage-stock-portfolio/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="universal-philosophy-of-investing">Universal Philosophy of Investing</h2>
<p>Whether engaging in low-cost index investing or high-intensity active speculation, the success of all market participants rests on a shared philosophical foundation.</p>
<h3 id="the-preparation-process-for-trading">The Preparation Process for Trading</h3>
<p>Investing and speculating are not driven by luck or impulse. They require the knowledge and discipline of a professional.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Acquire Knowledge</strong>: Before committing money, you must commit time, money, and effort to learning how markets function, how to manage risk, and how to analyze assets. Without intellectual investment, sustained returns are impossible.</li>
<li><strong>Professional Attitude</strong>: Treat trading the same way you would treat professional matters (like consulting a doctor or engineer). Never commit large sums to a position or strategy you do not fully understand.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="risk-awareness-and-capital-preservation">Risk Awareness and Capital Preservation</h3>
<p>Protecting your capital is the first priority of any trading activity.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Principles of Kinesiology</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-principles-of-kinesiology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:28:03 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-principles-of-kinesiology/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Stepping into the world of sports rehabilitation first requires a systematic framework for understanding how the human body moves. This framework consists of the two core branches of biomechanics—<strong>kinematics</strong> and <strong>kinetics</strong>—and their sub-branches.</p>
<p>You can think of understanding human movement like building a house. The following four concepts serve as the <strong>four key pillars</strong> that support this structure:</p>
<table>
  <thead>
      <tr>
          <th style="text-align: left">Core Pillar</th>
          <th style="text-align: left">Key Question</th>
      </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Kinematics</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>How does the body move?</strong> (Describing movement types and paths)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Osteokinematics</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>How do bones move in space?</strong> (Planes of motion, axes, degrees of freedom)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Arthrokinematics</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>How do joint surfaces move internally?</strong> (Roll, slide, spin)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Kinetics</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>What forces create movement?</strong> (Force, torque, levers)</td>
      </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<p>Understanding how these four pillars interact forms the foundation for analyzing movement, assessing posture, and designing rehabilitation programs.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze Industry in Stock Market?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-industry-in-stock-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-industry-in-stock-market/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Software Infrastructure</strong> is the foundational backbone that powers the modern digital economy and the age of artificial intelligence. The products and services in this industry do not directly face end consumers; instead, they serve as <strong>underlying technology platforms</strong>, supporting everything from enterprise operations and data analytics to advanced AI model training and all digital activities in between.</p>
<p>The Software Infrastructure industry attracts significant attention from capital markets due to its unique <strong>value model</strong>:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Create Infographics with AI?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-infographics-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:17:26 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-infographics-with-ai/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Infographics</strong> have become a key element for elevating content quality and increasing user engagement. Whether deepening a blog reader’s understanding or boosting the shareability of social media posts, a well-designed infographic can effectively visualize complex ideas, making them more persuasive and professional.</p>
<h2 id="method-1-reusing-existing-infographics">Method 1: Reusing Existing Infographics</h2>
<p>This is the fastest and most intuitive starting method, especially if you already have an idea of the design style you want, or simply want to save time on building a layout from scratch.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze a Cash Flow Statement?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-cash-flow-statement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:39:32 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-cash-flow-statement/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>The <strong>Cash Flow Statement (CFS)</strong> is the <strong>closest to reality</strong> among the three major financial statements. Unlike the income statement (which includes non-cash expenses) and the balance sheet (which is only a snapshot at a point in time), the CFS tracks the <strong>actual cash</strong> flowing in and out of the business over a <strong>specific period</strong>.</p>
<p>The ultimate value of a stock depends on how much <strong>free cash flow</strong> a company can generate throughout its lifecycle. The CFS directly reveals a company’s <strong>financial health</strong>, <strong>liquidity</strong>, and <strong>ability to service its debt</strong>.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>