<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/</link>
        <description>Chloe&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:00:35 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Landing Page Copy Commands Templates</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:00:35 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A thorough understanding of landing page structure and the copy characteristics of each module is essential to guide AI in producing appropriate, conversion-driven copy.
Copy Characteristics by Landing Page Module Hero Section Headline  Use &ldquo;verb + quantifiable result&rdquo; structure
Example: &ldquo;Generate 100+ Marketing Copies/Day&rdquo; (Better than &ldquo;Smart Copy Tool&rdquo;) Mobile: ≤9 Chinese characters, Desktop: ≤15 Chinese characters  Subheadline  Follow &ldquo;pain point scenario → solution&rdquo; formula
Example: &ldquo;Manual writing too slow?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>E-commerce Landing Page Conversion Secrets: How to Drive Sales Effectively</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 08:35:37 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is an E-commerce Landing Page? Definition An independent page accessed directly by users through ads/external links
 Direct Access Point: Users click from external channels like ads, social media links, or search results, jumping directly to this page without passing through the homepage or intermediate pages. Independent Design: Content focuses entirely on a single theme, with no navigation links to other pages.  Core Objectives Address specific user needs and drive targeted actions]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Protect Hugo Website Content from Being Copied</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:11:53 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[First, it must be clearly understood: There is no technical method that can 100% prevent content from being copied (methods like screenshots, manual rewriting, or crawlers can bypass protections). However, the following methods can significantly increase the difficulty of copying and reduce the risk of bulk theft.
Basic Protections (No Coding Required) Add Copyright Notices Include clear copyright information at the beginning/end of each article, for example:
 This article is licensed under CC BY-NC-ND 4.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Analyze SaaS Landing Page&#39;s Core Structure</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:57:44 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The first issue to consider: the positioning of the landing page in the site Considering different business goals, marketing costs and applicable scenarios, there are two forms of landing pages, each with its own advantages and disadvantages:
Specially built landing pages  Features:  Independent design: customized for specific marketing activities (such as advertising, brand activities, promotions, etc.), consistent with the official website design style, but with more streamlined and focused content No navigation bar interference: usually choose to hide the global navigation bar at the top, only retain the brand logo and important buttons, avoid users jumping to other pages, and expect to guide users to complete the target conversion actions (such as registration, purchase, etc.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Integrate Google Analytics with Hugo Website</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:07:56 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[After setting up your personal blog site using Hugo and GitHub Pages, you can integrate Google Analytics to monitor SEO performance and track detailed traffic metrics.
Configuration Steps 1. Log into Google Analytics 4 and Create a New Account Sign in with your Google account on the official website and create a new Google Analytics 4 (GA4) account.
Note: Google has fully transitioned to GA4, and the legacy Google Universal Analytics (UA) is deprecated.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Create Effective Location-Specific Landing Pages? 8 Key Elements</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:02:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[According to Google’s algorithm mechanics, the search results you receive on Google vary based on your geographic location (or the geographic preferences implied in your search terms). For businesses with physical local stores or those offering location-specific services, creating landing pages tailored to specific regions is essential. These pages not only help search engine crawlers better retrieve and understand your content but also enable visitors to quickly grasp what products or services are available near their residence.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Midjourney Advanced Tutorial</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-advanced-tutorial/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 07:54:32 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-advanced-tutorial/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In 《Midjourney Tutorial for Beginners》, we covered Midjourney&rsquo;s basic setup, commands, parameters, and image generation methods. This article will introduce more advanced techniques to help generate images that better match your expectations.
Advanced Prompt Parameters Quality The --quality or --q parameter enhances image details without increasing resolution:
 Default value: 1 Acceptable values: 0.25, 0.5, 1 (Values above 1 default to 1)  Stylize Lower Stylize values produce literal interpretations, while higher values increase artistic interpretation:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Midjourney Tutorial for Beginners</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-tutorial-for-beginners/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:54:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-tutorial-for-beginners/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Basic Settings Sending the /settings command to Midjourney Bot reveals configurable options:
Model Version Control The first dropdown menu selects Midjourney’s image generation models, which differ in artistic tendencies and parameter compatibility:
 Midjourney Model: Native model for photorealistic and stylized images. Default version is V6.1. Niji Model: Collaborative model with SpellBrush, optimized for anime/illustration styles. Current version: V6.  Stylization Control The second row controls artistic interpretation strength (higher values = more stylized results):]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Evaluate User Quality Across Different Digital Marketing Channels</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 08:56:32 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Is User Quality Assessment Critical? The core competition in digital marketing has shifted from &ldquo;acquiring traffic&rdquo; to &ldquo;screening high-quality users.&rdquo; With rising traffic costs and increasingly complex user behavior, blindly pursuing user quantity leads to resource waste: Low-quality users may generate short-term clicks but fail to deliver long-term returns (e.g., fake clicks, coupon abuse). By evaluating user quality, businesses can precisely identify high-value segments, allocate budgets to conversion-ready users, and avoid ineffective spending.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Cohort vs Non-Cohort in Digital Marketing</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 08:56:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Must We Distinguish Cohort from Non-Cohort? If we compare user behavior analysis to marathon analytics:
 Cohort Analysis tracks the same group of runners throughout the race (e.g., &ldquo;What percentage of users who joined in March completed the marathon?&quot;) Non-Cohort Analysis captures real-time snapshots of all runners (e.g., &ldquo;Current number of participants on the track&rdquo;)  An e-commerce platform made a critical error by using non-cohort analysis to observe a &ldquo;15% increase in click-through rate on the redesigned page&rdquo; and immediately rolled it out globally.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
