<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SEM - Tag - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/sem/</link>
        <description>SEM - Tag - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/sem/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Atlassian SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/atlassian-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/atlassian-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways  SEM Trend: From January 2012 to March 2024, Atlassian&rsquo;s paid traffic grew significantly, peaking in December 2020 with 471,348 average traffic but showed a decreasing trend by March 2024 with only 114,669 average traffic. SEM Keyword Strategy: By March 2024, Atlassian strategically balanced its keyword focus, achieving a notable traffic share of 35.54% from product-related keywords, with an average CPC of $5.85. SEM URL Traffic Distribution: As of March 2024, Atlassian&rsquo;s targeted URL strategy successfully directed 51.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Asana SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/asana-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/asana-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways  SEM Trend: From 2020 to 2023, Asana&rsquo;s average SEM traffic increased from 72,321 to 79,865, indicating a growth trend in paid traffic. SEM Keyword Strategy: The decrease in traffic from 92,970 to 49,549 between September 2023 and April 2024 suggests a need to reevaluate keyword strategies. SEM URL Traffic Distribution: In March 2024, the top landing pages indicated a diversified approach, targeting various user intents—from general campaign pages to specific feature pages.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Notion SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways:  SEM Trend: From June 2015 to January 2023, Notion&rsquo;s paid traffic demonstrated a consistent increase, peaking at an average of 18,585, indicating sustained growth in SEM efforts that likely enhanced overall market presence. SEM Keyword Strategy: During the period from January 2023 to September 2023, paid traffic surged to 148,906, suggesting a proactive and effective keyword targeting strategy during this phase, followed by a decline to 94,601 by March 2024, reflecting strategic adjustments or market shifts.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Smartsheet SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/smartsheet-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/smartsheet-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Analyze Smartsheet&rsquo;s SEM strategy from 2012 to 2024, focusing on keyword trends, SEM traffic, and URL distribution, with detailed traffic analysis for critical phases.
Takeaways  SEM Trend: From January 2012 to June 2020, Smartsheet experienced a relatively stable increase in average traffic, peaking at 44,667 visits. SEM Keyword Strategy: Traffic spiked significantly to 471,348 visits from June to December 2020, indicating a possibly aggressive or highly effective keyword strategy during this period.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>ClickUp SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways  SEM Trend: Traffic increased steadily from 11,400 in early 2017 to a peak of 77,844 in mid-2023, illustrating a successful scaling of SEM efforts over time. SEM Keyword Strategy: The top keyword traffic has been consistently high at 17,296 for the last three periods, reflecting ClickUp&rsquo;s focused and effective keyword targeting. SEM URL Traffic Distribution: Major traffic is concentrated on comparison and feature-specific pages, indicating strategic URL targeting to engage users at crucial decision-making points.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Wrike SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/wrike-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/wrike-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Analyze Wrike&rsquo;s SEM strategy across various phases from 2012 to 2024, highlighting traffic trends, keyword adjustments, and strategic URL targeting.
Takeaways  SEM Trend: Wrike&rsquo;s paid traffic peaked in July 2021 with an average of 115,764.85 visits, showing a shift in traffic dynamics. SEM Keyword Strategy: From 2012 to early 2021, there was a consistent increase in traffic, suggesting effective keyword optimizations. SEM URL Traffic Distribution: Traffic decreased to 35,308.31 by March 2024, indicating a need to reassess URL targeting strategies.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A PPC Competitor Analysis of Monday.com</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:46:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Brand Introduction Monday.com is a dynamic project management tool designed to simplify the way teams work together. Since its inception in 2012, Monday.com has emerged as a vibrant and innovative player in the SaaS industry, offering solutions that enable businesses to centralize task management, project tracking, and team collaboration in one platform.
What sets Monday.com apart is its highly customizable interface, which allows users from various industries including tech, finance, and creative sectors, to tailor the platform according to their specific project needs and workflows.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.
Background After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
