<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Obsidian on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/obsidian/</link><description>Recent content in Obsidian on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:31:21 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/obsidian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Practical Guide to Efficiently Managing Images in Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:31:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</guid><description>&lt;p>When taking notes in Obsidian, using images is almost inevitable. Copying and pasting images directly is indeed convenient, but over time you&amp;rsquo;ll find that the images are chaotically placed, resizing them is troublesome, and centering an image is even more difficult. Another pitfall is that when you delete an image from a note, the file doesn’t actually disappear but remains hidden in the root directory.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-exactly-are-images-in-obsidian">What Exactly Are Images in Obsidian?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When it comes to images, many people’s first thought is that &amp;ldquo;inserting an image means adding an image directly.&amp;rdquo; However, in Obsidian, images are more like references to &amp;ldquo;external files.&amp;rdquo; In other words, the images aren’t directly embedded in the note content but are stored in folders on your computer and then displayed in the notes through links or references.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Complete Guide to Installing and Getting Started with Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:13:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the era of information overload, more and more people are realizing that organizing and consolidating knowledge is more important than acquiring it. &lt;a href="https://obsidian.md/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Obsidian&lt;/a>, a note-taking app focused on &lt;strong>local knowledge management&lt;/strong>, has rapidly gained popularity among productivity enthusiasts and knowledge workers in recent years. It is not just another cloud-based note-taking tool but a &amp;ldquo;second brain&amp;rdquo; system that emphasizes &lt;strong>local storage, Markdown formatting, and linked thinking&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-core-philosophy-of-obsidian">The Core Philosophy of Obsidian&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At its core, Obsidian is about building a knowledge network that you control. Unlike traditional linear note-taking, Obsidian advocates for &lt;strong>nonlinear linked notes&lt;/strong>. By linking different notes, you can create a multidimensional, interconnected knowledge graph.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>