<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Google Ads on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/google-ads/</link><description>Recent content in Google Ads on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:36:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/google-ads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When to Use Performance Max vs. Demand Gen?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:36:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="whats-the-difference-between-performance-max-and-demand-gen-campaigns">What’s the Difference Between Performance Max and Demand Gen Campaigns?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Performance Max (PMax)&lt;/strong> is a fully automated campaign type by Google that allows advertisers to run a single campaign across all Google-owned channels—Search, Display, YouTube, Gmail, Discover, Maps, and more. It serves as a &lt;strong>complement to Search Ads&lt;/strong>, helping advertisers reach more potential customers across multiple touchpoints.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Demand Gen Campaigns&lt;/strong>, on the other hand, are designed for visually engaging platforms like YouTube and Google Discover. They focus on &lt;strong>sparking interest and creating demand&lt;/strong> through short-form videos and in-feed content—ideal for attracting new audiences to your brand or products.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Do Tariffs Affect PPC Advertising?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 09:39:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>The answer is definitely: Yes.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When new tariffs are imposed or existing ones are expanded, the &lt;strong>fundamental cost structure of goods&lt;/strong> changes, and companies&amp;rsquo; bidding behaviors also shift:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Some companies will increase their bids to secure the best ad positions, hoping to maintain existing profits.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Some companies will maintain their current bid levels in the short term, but ad spend may still rise (influenced by other advertisers increasing their bids, leading to an overall industry CPC increase). In the short term, they&amp;rsquo;ll choose to absorb costs to maintain market share.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Other companies will choose to exit this new round of competition, shifting their marketing budgets to other channels.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="what-are-tariffs">What are Tariffs?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A tariff (Customs Duty) is a mandatory tax levied by a sovereign nation or economic entity on &lt;strong>imported goods&lt;/strong> as they cross its customs border. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most common forms of trade barriers in international trade, enforced and collected by customs agencies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Do Google Ads for Business</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 07:57:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction-to-google-ads">Introduction to Google Ads&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="how-google-ads-works">How Google Ads Works&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://ads.google.com/home/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Google Ads&lt;/a> is an online advertising service that allows advertisers to display ads on Google search results pages, YouTube, and other partner websites through an auction system. When users search for keywords related to ads, Google will decide which ads to display in the search results based on a series of factors such as bids, ad quality, and relevance. The core of this process is keywords, and the keywords selected by advertisers will directly affect the exposure and click-through rate of ads.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Keyword Research and Targeting in the AI Era</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-keyword-research-and-targeting">What Is Keyword Research and Targeting?&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="keyword-research-understanding-how-users-search">Keyword Research: Understanding How Users Search&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Keyword research refers to analyzing data to identify the words or phrases users commonly use in search engines. These keywords are often not just single words but &lt;strong>search phrases with clear intent&lt;/strong>, such as:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>“Best coffee machine for small apartments”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“High value laptops in 2025”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“Which baby stroller brand is good”&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Through keyword research, we can understand what potential users truly care about, their preferences, and how they express themselves, allowing us to create content that better fits their search habits. Good keyword research makes content more aligned with real searches and improves its chances of being recommended by search engines.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improve CTR &amp; CVR: Master the Essential Skills of SEM Copy</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-sem-copy">What is SEM copy?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>SEM (search engine marketing) copy is text content created specifically for online advertising, designed to attract users to click and increase conversion rates. SEM copywriting should not only attract attention, but also be practical, able to guide potential users to take action, and directly affect the effectiveness and ROI of advertising.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="understand-the-composition-of-sem-ad-copy-three-main-elements">Understand the composition of SEM ad copy: three main elements&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/sem-ad-format_hu_ded4b6c4c95f87c7.png" 
 alt="" 
 width="1187" 
 height="108" 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Title&lt;/strong>: The part that users see at first glance in the search results. A striking title can effectively attract users&amp;rsquo; attention and stimulate their desire to click.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/assets/google-ads-specialist.webp" 
 alt="" 
 
 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="background">Background&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising. I have pushed new products, been in charge of high net worth products, experienced the whole account being blocked, and recently started to learn to recruit competent subordinates. Although the market situation is not optimistic in these years, from my personal experience, from the perspective of salary and market demand, overseas advertising specialist is still a good career choice. I hope this article can provide some reference for those who are interested in the position of Google Ads specialist.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>