<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Google Ads - Tag - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/google-ads/</link>
        <description>Google Ads - Tag - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:46:17 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/google-ads/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>A PPC Competitor Analysis of Monday.com</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:46:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Brand Introduction Monday.com is a dynamic project management tool designed to simplify the way teams work together. Since its inception in 2012, Monday.com has emerged as a vibrant and innovative player in the SaaS industry, offering solutions that enable businesses to centralize task management, project tracking, and team collaboration in one platform.
What sets Monday.com apart is its highly customizable interface, which allows users from various industries including tech, finance, and creative sectors, to tailor the platform according to their specific project needs and workflows.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.
Background After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
