<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Hugo - Category - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/hugo/</link>
        <description>Hugo - Category - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:11:53 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/hugo/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Protect Hugo Website Content from Being Copied</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:11:53 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[First, it must be clearly understood: There is no technical method that can 100% prevent content from being copied (methods like screenshots, manual rewriting, or crawlers can bypass protections). However, the following methods can significantly increase the difficulty of copying and reduce the risk of bulk theft.
Basic Protections (No Coding Required) Add Copyright Notices Include clear copyright information at the beginning/end of each article, for example:
 This article is licensed under CC BY-NC-ND 4.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Integrate Google Analytics with Hugo Website</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:07:56 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[After setting up your personal blog site using Hugo and GitHub Pages, you can integrate Google Analytics to monitor SEO performance and track detailed traffic metrics.
Configuration Steps 1. Log into Google Analytics 4 and Create a New Account Sign in with your Google account on the official website and create a new Google Analytics 4 (GA4) account.
Note: Google has fully transitioned to GA4, and the legacy Google Universal Analytics (UA) is deprecated.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to use Hugo to Build a Blog and Deploy it to Github Page</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/hugo-github-pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 07:57:53 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/hugo-github-pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[1. Install Hugo  Windows:  First install the choco package manager, run cmd under administrator rights, and execute the following command:
1 2 3 4  powershell -NoProfile -ExecutionPolicy unrestricted -Command &#34;iex ((new-object net.webclient).DownloadString(&#39;https://chocolatey.org/install.ps1&#39;))&#34; # Set environment variables SET PATH=%PATH%;%ALLUSERSPROFILE%\chocolatey\bin   Then use choco to install hugo:
choco install hugo -confirm
 MacOs:  Install using brew command:
brew install hugo
 Linux:  Install using snap command:]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
