<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Finance on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/finance/</link><description>Recent content in Finance on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:51:13 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Read P/E Ratio?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:51:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Price-to-Earnings Ratio (P/E Ratio)&lt;/strong> is one of the most commonly used metrics for assessing a stock’s valuation. It directly compares a stock’s &lt;strong>price&lt;/strong> to the company’s &lt;strong>earnings power&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>What is it?&lt;/strong>
The P/E ratio, simply put, tells you how many dollars you must pay in price for &lt;strong>every $1 of profit&lt;/strong> a company earns.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>What does it measure?&lt;/strong>
The P/E ratio reflects the market’s &lt;strong>expectations&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>premium&lt;/strong> for a company. For example, if a stock has a P/E of &lt;strong>20×&lt;/strong>, it means investors are willing to purchase the stock at 20 times the company’s annual earnings.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Read Financial Statements of a Company?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 07:54:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</guid><description>&lt;p>Financial statements are reports that companies prepare periodically (usually quarterly or annually) to &lt;strong>summarize and report&lt;/strong> their business activities and financial performance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Warren Buffett has referred to financial statements as the &lt;strong>“language of business.”&lt;/strong> For investors, managers, and creditors, they are essential tools for understanding a company’s financial health, profitability, and ability to meet its obligations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are three core financial statements, and together they provide a complete view of a company from different perspectives:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introduction to Volume Analysis: Using Volume to Verify the Reliability of Price Movements</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:09:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</guid><description>&lt;p>When you open any financial chart, your eyes will undoubtedly be drawn first to the fluctuations in price. However, while most beginners focus on price, they often overlook another critical foundational element on the chart — &lt;strong>volume&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In professional market analysis, &lt;strong>price&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>volume&lt;/strong> are the two core pillars for determining market trends. Price tells us “what has changed,” while volume reveals the “strength behind the move” and the &lt;strong>market consensus&lt;/strong>. A price move without the support of volume is like a rumor without factual basis — it can reverse at any time.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Read Stocks — A Beginner’s Guide Based on Yahoo Finance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:14:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the world of investing! When you first open a stock app or financial website, have you ever felt overwhelmed by the dense numbers, curves, and strange professional abbreviations (such as P/E, Beta, Volume) on the page?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For investment beginners, the first task in understanding a stock is to read that seemingly complicated &lt;strong>stock quote sheet&lt;/strong>. Once you grasp the meaning of these data points, you can quickly judge a stock’s current value, market activity, and potential risk.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>