<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Landing Page on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/landing-page/</link><description>Recent content in Landing Page on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:00:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/landing-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Landing Page Copy Commands Templates</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:00:35 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</guid><description>&lt;p>A thorough understanding of landing page structure and the copy characteristics of each module is essential to guide AI in producing appropriate, conversion-driven copy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="copy-characteristics-by-landing-page-module">Copy Characteristics by Landing Page Module&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="hero-section">Hero Section&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="headline">Headline&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Use &amp;ldquo;verb + quantifiable result&amp;rdquo; structure&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example:&lt;/em> &amp;ldquo;Generate 100+ Marketing Copies/Day&amp;rdquo; (Better than &amp;ldquo;Smart Copy Tool&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mobile: ≤9 Chinese characters, Desktop: ≤15 Chinese characters&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="subheadline">Subheadline&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Follow &amp;ldquo;pain point scenario → solution&amp;rdquo; formula&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example:&lt;/em> &amp;ldquo;Manual writing too slow? AI 10x speed ensures daily updates&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="cta-button">CTA Button&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Build triple motivation:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Urgency: &amp;ldquo;Last 3 free spots&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Low-barrier commitment: &amp;ldquo;Try free in 10 seconds&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Loss aversion: &amp;ldquo;Wasting ¥37,200/year?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="featuresbenefits-module">Features/Benefits Module&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="feature-description">Feature Description&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Technical term translation formula:&lt;br>
&amp;ldquo;[Technical term] → [User action] → [Verifiable result]&amp;rdquo;&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example:&lt;/em> &amp;ldquo;NLP algorithm → Auto-match industry keywords → 59% higher read completion&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="benefit-tiering">Benefit Tiering&lt;/h4>
&lt;table>
 &lt;thead>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;th>Tier&lt;/th>
 &lt;th>Focus&lt;/th>
 &lt;th>Example&lt;/th>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;/thead>
 &lt;tbody>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>Core Value&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Solve specific problems&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>1-minute draft generation&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>Advanced Value&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Prevent risks&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Auto compliance check&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>Strategic Value&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Create extended benefits&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Boost brand search index&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;h3 id="social-proof-module">Social Proof Module&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="testimonials">Testimonials&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Four-element structure:&lt;br>
&amp;ldquo;[Identity] encountered [quantified problem] in [specific scenario], achieved [contrast result] after use&amp;rdquo;&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example:&lt;/em> &amp;ldquo;Maternal e-commerce operator producing 50 copies/day with 15% error rate → 4x efficiency &amp;amp; zero errors&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="data-presentation">Data Presentation&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Regular data: Magnify base numbers (&amp;ldquo;152,370+ users served&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sensitive data: Precise decimals (&amp;ldquo;92.37% approval rate&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Dynamic data: Create urgency (&amp;ldquo;1 new user every 3 seconds&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="bottom-navigation">Bottom Navigation&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="primary-cta-enhancement">Primary CTA Enhancement&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Value reinforcement: &amp;ldquo;Reiterating: You&amp;rsquo;ll gain ______&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cost minimization: &amp;ldquo;Only requires ______ (time/money)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="exit-intent-strategy">Exit-Intent Strategy&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Active retention:&lt;br>
&amp;ldquo;Confirm before leaving: Have you obtained [free resource]?&amp;rdquo;&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example:&lt;/em> &amp;ldquo;Confirm: Have you downloaded《2024 Copy Trends Whitepaper》?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Secondary option:&lt;br>
&amp;ldquo;Not ready? Subscribe to weekly case studies (Wednesdays)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="prohibited-copy-types">Prohibited Copy Types&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Vague adjectives: &amp;ldquo;High-quality&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Professional&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Leading&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ambiguous claims: &amp;ldquo;Improve efficiency&amp;rdquo; → Quantify instead&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Passive voice: &amp;ldquo;You will get&amp;rdquo; → Change to &amp;ldquo;Claim now&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="is-ai-suitable-for-landing-page-copy-generation">Is AI Suitable for Landing Page Copy Generation?&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="core-value-of-ai-generation">Core Value of AI Generation&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="scalable-production">Scalable Production&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Batch generation&lt;/strong>: 15-20 headline variations per command&lt;br>
&lt;em>Example prompt:&lt;/em>&lt;br>
&amp;ldquo;Generate 10 ecommerce headlines covering urgency, clear benefits, and scenarios&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>E-commerce Landing Page Conversion Secrets: How to Drive Sales Effectively</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 08:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-an-e-commerce-landing-page">What is an E-commerce Landing Page?&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="definition">Definition&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>An independent page accessed directly by users through ads/external links&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Direct Access Point&lt;/strong>: Users click from external channels like ads, social media links, or search results, jumping directly to this page without passing through the homepage or intermediate pages.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Independent Design&lt;/strong>: Content focuses entirely on a single theme, with no navigation links to other pages.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="core-objectives">Core Objectives&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Address specific user needs and drive targeted actions&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Analyze SaaS Landing Page's Core Structure</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:57:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-first-issue-to-consider-the-positioning-of-the-landing-page-in-the-site">The first issue to consider: the positioning of the landing page in the site&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Considering different business goals, marketing costs and applicable scenarios, there are two forms of landing pages, each with its own advantages and disadvantages:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="specially-built-landing-pages">Specially built landing pages&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Features:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Independent design: customized for specific marketing activities (such as advertising, brand activities, promotions, etc.), consistent with the official website design style, but with more streamlined and focused content&lt;/li>
&lt;li>No navigation bar interference: usually choose to hide the global navigation bar at the top, only retain the brand logo and important buttons, avoid users jumping to other pages, and expect to guide users to complete the target conversion actions (such as registration, purchase, etc.)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Advantages:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>High conversion rate: present as much information as possible in a smaller layout, the content accurately matches user needs, reduces interference, and helps to improve conversion rate.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Support fast iteration: because it is a customized page, it has high flexibility in adjusting content and design, and will not affect other businesses.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Easy data analysis: the overall CTA logic of the page is basically consistent, the number of user paths is small, and only a small number of channels use this page, which is convenient for subsequent analysis of data effects.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Disadvantages:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Requires additional design and development costs.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Weak brand credibility: Users may want to know more about the website, but dedicated landing pages generally do not provide an obvious entrance to other pages.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="existing-pages-on-the-official-website">Existing pages on the official website&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Features:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Reuse existing content: Directly use a page on the official website (such as the homepage, product page, article page) as the landing page.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Keep the top navigation bar: Users can understand the general structure of the website through the navigation bar and freely jump to the page they are interested in.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Advantages:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Cost savings: No additional design and development involved.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Strengthen brand consistency: Ensure the overall experience of users on the official website, and at the same time have user comments, third-party evaluation certificates and other pages as support for brand credibility.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Disadvantages:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Relatively low conversion rate: The official website content is more brand-oriented, and the information is not focused enough. Users are easily distracted by other content such as navigation bars and internal links.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Difficult to iterate quickly and data is mixed: Different channels will use official website pages, and content and design adjustments require the consent of multiple parties before they can be promoted. The multiple behavioral paths of users on the website also increase the difficulty of data analysis.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>As for which form or website structure is better, it still depends on the brand&amp;rsquo;s own focus and marketing strategy. Take the landing page of monday.com as an example: it is not difficult to find that monday.com uses the official website homepage (&lt;a href="https://monday.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">https://monday.com/&lt;/a>) to accept users who search for its brand words, and uses dedicated landing pages (such as &lt;a href="https://monday.com/ap/project-management" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">https://monday.com/ap/project-management&lt;/a>) to meet users who search for other keywords (here I use project management).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Create Effective Location-Specific Landing Pages? 8 Key Elements</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:02:05 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</guid><description>&lt;p>According to Google’s algorithm mechanics, the search results you receive on Google vary based on your geographic location (or the geographic preferences implied in your search terms). For businesses with physical local stores or those offering location-specific services, creating landing pages tailored to specific regions is essential. These pages not only help search engine crawlers better retrieve and understand your content but also enable visitors to quickly grasp what products or services are available near their residence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Best Landing Page Layouts with Webform</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</guid><description>&lt;p>Landing page design is an integral part of website optimization and marketing activities. Among all the elements that enhance user interaction, Webform plays a key role. Whether it is collecting potential customer information, obtaining user feedback, or driving sales, the layout and design of Webform directly affect the conversion rate. This article will explore in depth how to create an efficient landing page by optimizing form design and page layout.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Choose a Landing Page Name Generator with SEO Keywords</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:32:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</guid><description>&lt;p>In SEO optimization, the visibility and click-through rate of a website depend on multiple factors, and the optimization of &lt;strong>domain name&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>landing page name&lt;/strong> is a crucial part. Although both are important components of website SEO, their optimization focuses are different. Understanding the difference between the two will help you develop a more accurate SEO strategy for your website, thereby improving rankings and user conversion rates. On this basis, this article provides recommendations for two types of tools: &amp;ldquo;domain name generation tool&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;page title optimization tool&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>