<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:02:30 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>SEO Audit My Site Using SEMrush</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:02:30 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have been suffering from the index of website pages. I have published new articles, but the number of pages not indexed has increased. So I used SEMrush to audit the website as a whole and made some corrections for specific problems to see if the index situation will improve.
The Site audit function is used. After entering the domain name and setting the number of pages to crawl, wait for about ten minutes and you can get an analysis report: The core logic between several indicators:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Best Landing Page Layouts with Webform</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Landing page design is an integral part of website optimization and marketing activities. Among all the elements that enhance user interaction, Webform plays a key role. Whether it is collecting potential customer information, obtaining user feedback, or driving sales, the layout and design of Webform directly affect the conversion rate. This article will explore in depth how to create an efficient landing page by optimizing form design and page layout.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Choose a Landing Page Name Generator with SEO Keywords</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:32:08 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In SEO optimization, the visibility and click-through rate of a website depend on multiple factors, and the optimization of domain name and landing page name is a crucial part. Although both are important components of website SEO, their optimization focuses are different. Understanding the difference between the two will help you develop a more accurate SEO strategy for your website, thereby improving rankings and user conversion rates. On this basis, this article provides recommendations for two types of tools: &ldquo;domain name generation tool&rdquo; and &ldquo;page title optimization tool&rdquo;.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Do Google Ads for Business</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 07:57:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction to Google Ads How Google Ads Works Google Ads is an online advertising service that allows advertisers to display ads on Google search results pages, YouTube, and other partner websites through an auction system. When users search for keywords related to ads, Google will decide which ads to display in the search results based on a series of factors such as bids, ad quality, and relevance. The core of this process is keywords, and the keywords selected by advertisers will directly affect the exposure and click-through rate of ads.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>PPC Keyword Analysis Guide</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ppc-keyword-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 07:56:50 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ppc-keyword-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pay-per-click (PPC) advertising has become an important tool for companies to gain traffic and increase conversions. The selection of PPC keywords is directly related to the effectiveness of advertising and the return on investment (ROI). Effective keywords can help ads accurately reach the target audience and ensure that the company&rsquo;s ads stand out when potential customers search for relevant information.
Classification of PPC keywords PPC keywords are specific words or phrases selected by advertisers when using pay-per-click advertising, which directly affects the exposure and conversion rate of ads.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Google Conversion Tracking</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 08:44:22 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Google conversion tracking is a feature provided by Google that tracks key actions taken by users after interacting with ads. Whether it is a purchase after clicking an ad, filling out a form, making a phone call, or downloading an app, Google can capture these user behaviors and quantify them into data. This data can not only help you determine whether your ads are effective, but also clearly know which advertising campaigns are driving business growth.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Understand Tacit Knowledge in One Article</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/tacit-knowledge/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:10:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/tacit-knowledge/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Tacit Knowledge? Tacit knowledge, also known as implicit knowledge, is a type of knowledge that is difficult to formalize and personal, usually based on experience, intuition, and perception. Unlike explicit knowledge, tacit knowledge is difficult to convey through words, data, or formulas. It is often deeply embedded in an individual&rsquo;s behavior, skills, or culture, and relies on practice and personal experience to acquire.
For example, learning to ride a bicycle is a typical example of tacit knowledge.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Best AdWords Reports: The Ultimate Guide to Boosting Your Ads Performance</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:11:07 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are AdWords reports? The core of advertising optimization lies in data-driven decision-making, and Google AdWords (now known as Google Ads) reports are the key tools to achieve this goal. With AdWords reports, advertisers can gain in-depth insights into the performance of their campaigns and find areas that need to be optimized to maximize the effectiveness and return on investment (ROI) of their ads.
AdWords reports are data reports generated by the Google Ads platform that can display various key data of the campaign in detail, including impressions, click-through rate, conversion rate, cost, etc.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Calculate CPC of Keywords</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cpc-of-keywords/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 08:45:12 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cpc-of-keywords/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is CPC? Cost per click (CPC) is an online advertising billing model where advertisers pay based on the number of times a user clicks on their ad. This model is very common in search engine advertising and social media advertising, allowing advertisers to precisely control their budgets and ensure that every penny brings the attention of potential customers.
Imagine that when you enter a keyword into a search engine, multiple ads appear on the results page.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Guide to Search Engine Positioning Software</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:11:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Search Engine Positioning Software Search Engine Positioning Software is a tool that helps website managers, marketers, and SEO experts track and optimize website rankings on search engine results pages (SERPs). It helps companies improve website visibility in a competitive market by monitoring keyword ranking changes, analyzing competitor website performance, and providing improvement suggestions.
In SEO (search engine optimization), search engine positioning software plays a vital role. The goal of SEO is to improve the natural ranking of a website in search engines by optimizing its content and structure.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
