<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 08:49:10 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>What Are the Advantages of Bing Shopping Ads?</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/bing-shopping-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 08:49:10 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/bing-shopping-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Bing&rsquo;s Market Share Continues to Grow According to StatCounter (2024 data), Bing holds approximately 3.42% of the global search engine market share, making it the second-largest search engine after Google.
In the U.S. market, Bing&rsquo;s search engine market share stands at 7.85%, showing slight growth from 5.97% in 2021. In 2014, Bing reached its peak U.S. market share at 9.9%.
Why Focus on Bing Ads? High-Purchasing-Power User Base  Significant Male Demographic: Data from SimilarWeb shows that two-thirds (64.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Comprehensive Guide to Digital Advertising Types</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/types-of-digital-advertising/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 07:49:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/types-of-digital-advertising/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Digital advertising reaches target audiences through diverse formats. This article introduces 11 mainstream advertising types using the Definition→Targeting Methods→Format Breakdown→Main Platforms structure.
1. Search Ads Search ads are text or dynamic ads triggered by user search keywords on search engines (e.g., Google, Bing), typically appearing at the top, bottom, or sidebar of search engine results pages (SERPs). Their core logic is capturing active search intent by matching keywords to deliver relevant ads.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>SEO Configuration for Hugo Multilingual Websites</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-configuration-for-hugo-multilingual-websites/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:16:35 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-configuration-for-hugo-multilingual-websites/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Potential Reasons Why Hugo Multilingual Sites Are Not Properly Indexed by Search Engines I recently noticed an issue with newly published articles: Google only indexes one language version of the same article (either Chinese or English). There are occasional cases where both versions get indexed, but this is rare. I began investigating potential configuration issues, which may include:
Multilingual Configuration Issues  Ensure proper multilingual configuration in config.toml or config.yaml, e.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Minimalist 3D Illustration Style Prompt (With Complete Code)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/minimalist-3d-illustration-style-prompt/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:47:11 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/minimalist-3d-illustration-style-prompt/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Characteristics of Minimalist 3D Illustration Style   Basic Geometric Shapes
Built upon simple geometric forms (spheres, cubes, cylinders), avoiding complex structures. Visual subjects are formed through combination or deformation.
  Low Detail Processing
Reduce textures and decorative details on model surfaces, retaining only essential contour features to emphasize clean overall forms.
  Soft Color Schemes
Predominantly use low-saturation tones (e.g., Morandi color palette) with gentle light-dark contrasts, avoiding high contrast or fluorescent colors.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Landing Page Copy Commands Templates</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:00:35 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/command-for-creating-landing-page-copy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A thorough understanding of landing page structure and the copy characteristics of each module is essential to guide AI in producing appropriate, conversion-driven copy.
Copy Characteristics by Landing Page Module Hero Section Headline  Use &ldquo;verb + quantifiable result&rdquo; structure
Example: &ldquo;Generate 100+ Marketing Copies/Day&rdquo; (Better than &ldquo;Smart Copy Tool&rdquo;) Mobile: ≤9 Chinese characters, Desktop: ≤15 Chinese characters  Subheadline  Follow &ldquo;pain point scenario → solution&rdquo; formula
Example: &ldquo;Manual writing too slow?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>E-commerce Landing Page Conversion Secrets: How to Drive Sales Effectively</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 08:35:37 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ecommerce-landing-page/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is an E-commerce Landing Page? Definition An independent page accessed directly by users through ads/external links
 Direct Access Point: Users click from external channels like ads, social media links, or search results, jumping directly to this page without passing through the homepage or intermediate pages. Independent Design: Content focuses entirely on a single theme, with no navigation links to other pages.  Core Objectives Address specific user needs and drive targeted actions]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Protect Hugo Website Content from Being Copied</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:11:53 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/protect-hugo-website-content-from-being-copied/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[First, it must be clearly understood: There is no technical method that can 100% prevent content from being copied (methods like screenshots, manual rewriting, or crawlers can bypass protections). However, the following methods can significantly increase the difficulty of copying and reduce the risk of bulk theft.
Basic Protections (No Coding Required) Add Copyright Notices Include clear copyright information at the beginning/end of each article, for example:
 This article is licensed under CC BY-NC-ND 4.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Analyze SaaS Landing Page&#39;s Core Structure</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:57:44 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/saas-landing-page/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The first issue to consider: the positioning of the landing page in the site Considering different business goals, marketing costs and applicable scenarios, there are two forms of landing pages, each with its own advantages and disadvantages:
Specially built landing pages  Features:  Independent design: customized for specific marketing activities (such as advertising, brand activities, promotions, etc.), consistent with the official website design style, but with more streamlined and focused content No navigation bar interference: usually choose to hide the global navigation bar at the top, only retain the brand logo and important buttons, avoid users jumping to other pages, and expect to guide users to complete the target conversion actions (such as registration, purchase, etc.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Integrate Google Analytics with Hugo Website</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:07:56 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[After setting up your personal blog site using Hugo and GitHub Pages, you can integrate Google Analytics to monitor SEO performance and track detailed traffic metrics.
Configuration Steps 1. Log into Google Analytics 4 and Create a New Account Sign in with your Google account on the official website and create a new Google Analytics 4 (GA4) account.
Note: Google has fully transitioned to GA4, and the legacy Google Universal Analytics (UA) is deprecated.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Create Effective Location-Specific Landing Pages? 8 Key Elements</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:02:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[According to Google’s algorithm mechanics, the search results you receive on Google vary based on your geographic location (or the geographic preferences implied in your search terms). For businesses with physical local stores or those offering location-specific services, creating landing pages tailored to specific regions is essential. These pages not only help search engine crawlers better retrieve and understand your content but also enable visitors to quickly grasp what products or services are available near their residence.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
