<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:43:59 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Max vs. Manual: Who Wins at Keyword Matching?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-search-keyword-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:42:40 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-search-keyword-insights/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>AI is becoming increasingly important in the advertising world, and <strong><a href="https://blog.google/products/ads-commerce/google-ai-max-for-search-campaigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max for Search</a></strong> from Google is a perfect example. Its core concept is simple: you provide some basic information, and the AI finds the most relevant users, automating your ad campaigns. For advertisers, this sounds very convenient.</p>
<p>But a question quickly arises: how exactly does this powerful AI work? Its internal decision-making process is invisible to us. We know what we put in and what comes out, but everything in between is like a &ldquo;black box.&rdquo;</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Maximize AdSense Revenue?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-improve-adsense-revenue/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:17:27 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-improve-adsense-revenue/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>If you have already followed the <a href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-earn-money-with-adsense/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">previous guide</a> and successfully placed <strong>Google AdSense</strong> ads on your website, congratulations — you’ve taken the first step toward earning! However, many new site owners find that <strong>traffic comes, but revenue is not ideal</strong>. At this point, improving AdSense revenue becomes crucial.</p>
<h2 id="understanding-adsense-revenue-mechanism">Understanding AdSense Revenue Mechanism</h2>
<p>Before optimizing revenue, it’s essential to understand <strong>how AdSense makes money</strong>. Simply put, your website traffic and ad interactions determine revenue, which mainly comes from <strong>ad impressions (RPM)</strong> and <strong>ad clicks (CPC)</strong>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Complete Practical Guide - How to Earn Money with Google AdSense?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-earn-money-with-adsense/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:16:01 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-earn-money-with-adsense/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever thought that your website or YouTube channel could be more than just a hobby platform and actually generate a steady, ongoing income? For beginner content creators, figuring out how to monetize traffic is often the top concern.</p>
<p>Among many options, <strong>Google AdSense</strong> is arguably the most common and beginner-friendly tool. It allows you to earn revenue by displaying ads while you focus on creating content, without requiring complex operations.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How Agents and Knowledge Bases Enable AI to Truly Work for You</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/agent-vs-knowledge-base/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 19:59:29 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/agent-vs-knowledge-base/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>You may have experienced this: when chatting with AI, it can help you write poems, generate code, or even explain complex concepts like a teacher — its intelligence can be astonishing. But when you ask it for your company’s latest sales data, or to book a meeting room, it suddenly seems to “forget” everything and cannot respond. Why does this happen?</p>
<p>The reason is that most AI models do not directly access your proprietary information; they mostly rely on general knowledge learned from training data. To enable AI to truly “get things done,” it requires two key components: <strong>Agents</strong> and <strong>Knowledge Bases</strong>. The agent serves as AI’s “action brain,” capable of understanding instructions, invoking tools, and executing tasks; the knowledge base acts as AI’s “memory repository,” storing enterprise data, documents, and rules so the AI can access and utilize up-to-date information.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>AI Beginner's Guide: General-Purpose Model vs Inference Model</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/inference-model-vs-general-purpose-model/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:09:01 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/inference-model-vs-general-purpose-model/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>We actually interact with AI every day.
Opening ChatGPT to draft a copy? That’s AI.
Using your phone to take a photo of a dish and get calorie information? That’s also AI.
Translation apps, speech-to-text, automatic recognition in your photo library—all rely on AI.</p>
<p>They may look similar, but the underlying mechanisms are completely different.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>General-Purpose Model</strong>: Can handle a wide range of tasks. ChatGPT is an example. In academia, you might also hear the term <strong>Foundation Model</strong>, while in practical use, people often refer to <strong>Large Language Model (LLM)</strong>.</li>
<li><strong>Inference Model</strong>: Specialized for a specific type of task, such as image recognition, translation, or speech recognition. Sometimes called <strong>Deployment Model</strong> or <strong>Task-Specific Model</strong>, emphasizing optimization for specific tasks.</li>
</ul>
<p>Why differentiate? Because it determines how you should use them:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate B2B Marketing?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-b2b-marketing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:47:22 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-b2b-marketing/</guid><description>&lt;p>B2B and B2C marketing both require effectiveness measurement, but their focus differs. B2C marketing typically targets individual consumers, with shorter decision chains and higher purchase frequency. Therefore, B2C metrics often emphasize immediate conversions, user engagement, and customer lifetime value. B2B marketing, on the other hand, targets business clients, with more complex purchasing decisions, longer cycles, and multiple decision-makers. As a result, B2B marketing focuses more on lead quality, sales conversion rates, and the contribution of marketing to the entire sales funnel.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introduction to Content Engineering: Making Content Smarter and More Usable</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:06:25 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="why-should-we-care-about-content">Why Should We Care About Content?</h2>
<p>In today’s digital world, we interact with &ldquo;content&rdquo; almost every day. Whether browsing websites, scrolling through short videos, using mobile apps, or chatting with smart assistants, the core of these experiences is various forms of content. In other words, content has become the primary medium through which we communicate, gather information, and make decisions.</p>
<p>However, despite being ubiquitous, content often faces a common problem: <strong>fragmentation and duplication</strong>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Basics of Ad Networks and Formats</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basics-of-ad-networks-and-formats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:31:07 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basics-of-ad-networks-and-formats/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-an-ad-network">What Is an Ad Network?</h2>
<p>In the internet advertising ecosystem, an <strong>ad network</strong> plays a crucial but often overlooked role. Simply put, it acts like a middleman, connecting <strong>advertisers</strong> and <strong>publishers</strong>, enabling ads to circulate efficiently across websites, apps, and video platforms.</p>
<p>Without ad networks, advertisers would need to negotiate with each media individually, which is very inefficient. At the same time, small and medium-sized websites or apps would struggle to connect with enough advertisers, often leaving ad space unsold. Ad networks solve this “two-sided problem.”</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Find the Best Monetization Path for My Business</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-find-the-best-monetization-path-for-my-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:17:01 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-find-the-best-monetization-path-for-my-business/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In today&rsquo;s highly competitive business environment, the question of &ldquo;how to make money&rdquo; is no longer the only challenge. The real question is: <strong>how to find a sustainable monetization path that fits your business</strong>.</p>
<p>Different products and companies face varying user groups, product types, and market environments. For some businesses, leveraging large-scale traffic for advertising is a shortcut. Others rely on subscriptions or value-added services to generate revenue. Some companies adopt a hybrid model to balance short-term gains with long-term value.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate and Improve AI Max Performance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:55:22 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</guid><description>&lt;p>In Google Ads, AI Max is not a separate campaign type but a set of AI enhancements embedded within existing search ads. As a result, the methods for viewing data and analyzing performance are integrated into your Search campaign reports.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once AI Max is enabled, advertisers are most concerned with performance: how do features like expanded keyword matching, automatically generated ad copy, and AI-selected landing pages impact traffic and conversions? In Google Ads, we can use several key reports to gain deeper insights into AI Max performance.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>