<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:47:22 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Evaluate B2b Marketing?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-b2b-marketing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:47:22 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-b2b-marketing/</guid><description>&lt;p>B2B and B2C marketing both require effectiveness measurement, but their focus differs. B2C marketing typically targets individual consumers, with shorter decision chains and higher purchase frequency. Therefore, B2C metrics often emphasize immediate conversions, user engagement, and customer lifetime value. B2B marketing, on the other hand, targets business clients, with more complex purchasing decisions, longer cycles, and multiple decision-makers. As a result, B2B marketing focuses more on lead quality, sales conversion rates, and the contribution of marketing to the entire sales funnel.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introduction to Content Engineering: Making Content Smarter and More Usable</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:06:25 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="why-should-we-care-about-content">Why Should We Care About Content?</h2>
<p>In today’s digital world, we interact with &ldquo;content&rdquo; almost every day. Whether browsing websites, scrolling through short videos, using mobile apps, or chatting with smart assistants, the core of these experiences is various forms of content. In other words, content has become the primary medium through which we communicate, gather information, and make decisions.</p>
<p>However, despite being ubiquitous, content often faces a common problem: <strong>fragmentation and duplication</strong>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Basics of Ad Networks and Formats</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basics-of-ad-networks-and-formats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:31:07 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basics-of-ad-networks-and-formats/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-an-ad-network">What Is an Ad Network?</h2>
<p>In the internet advertising ecosystem, an <strong>ad network</strong> plays a crucial but often overlooked role. Simply put, it acts like a middleman, connecting <strong>advertisers</strong> and <strong>publishers</strong>, enabling ads to circulate efficiently across websites, apps, and video platforms.</p>
<p>Without ad networks, advertisers would need to negotiate with each media individually, which is very inefficient. At the same time, small and medium-sized websites or apps would struggle to connect with enough advertisers, often leaving ad space unsold. Ad networks solve this “two-sided problem.”</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Find the Best Monetization Path for My Business</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-find-the-best-monetization-path-for-my-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:17:01 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-find-the-best-monetization-path-for-my-business/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In today&rsquo;s highly competitive business environment, the question of &ldquo;how to make money&rdquo; is no longer the only challenge. The real question is: <strong>how to find a sustainable monetization path that fits your business</strong>.</p>
<p>Different products and companies face varying user groups, product types, and market environments. For some businesses, leveraging large-scale traffic for advertising is a shortcut. Others rely on subscriptions or value-added services to generate revenue. Some companies adopt a hybrid model to balance short-term gains with long-term value.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate and Improve AI Max Performance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:55:22 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</guid><description>&lt;p>In Google Ads, AI Max is not a separate campaign type but a set of AI enhancements embedded within existing search ads. As a result, the methods for viewing data and analyzing performance are integrated into your Search campaign reports.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once AI Max is enabled, advertisers are most concerned with performance: how do features like expanded keyword matching, automatically generated ad copy, and AI-selected landing pages impact traffic and conversions? In Google Ads, we can use several key reports to gain deeper insights into AI Max performance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is Google AI Max for Search?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-is-google-ai-max/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:10:18 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-is-google-ai-max/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you’re running search ads, you’re probably familiar with this scenario: you open Google Ads in the morning, and your account is full of keywords to optimize. Some keywords have spent a lot but brought no conversions, while some long-tail searches you never thought of are showing up in the reports. You spend half a day adding and excluding keywords, yet it feels like you can never keep up with changing search behavior.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Basic Concepts of Commercialization</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-concepts-of-commercialization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:58:46 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/basic-concepts-of-commercialization/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-is-commercialization">What is Commercialization?</h2>
<p>When people hear “commercialization,” the first thought is often “making money.” That’s not wrong—turning a business, product, or traffic into revenue is indeed the core goal. However, commercialization can be understood in <strong>two perspectives: narrow and broad</strong>.</p>
<h3 id="narrow-perspective-result-oriented-ways-to-make-money">Narrow Perspective: Result-Oriented Ways to Make Money</h3>
<p>From the most direct angle, commercialization is about converting your business directly into revenue. Some simple examples include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Product Sales</strong>: Selling goods or services directly generates income, e.g., e-commerce selling clothing or online platforms selling courses.</li>
<li><strong>Advertising Monetization</strong>: Earning revenue from traffic, e.g., social media or short-video platforms displaying ads while users browse content.</li>
<li><strong>Membership Fees</strong>: Users pay for a better experience or exclusive content, e.g., premium subscriptions.</li>
</ul>
<p>This perspective is obvious: it focuses on <strong>“how to make money”</strong>, emphasizing results. The key question is how your business generates revenue from users and how to maximize short-term returns.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Make Integrated Marketing Strategy</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-make-integrated-marketing-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:57:49 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-make-integrated-marketing-strategy/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="1-user-insights-and-journey-analysis">1. User Insights and Journey Analysis</h2>
<p>Before formulating any integrated marketing strategy, in-depth user insights and journey analysis are indispensable foundational work. They help the brand truly understand who the target users are, their needs and pain points, as well as their behavior patterns along the purchase path, thus providing a scientific basis for subsequent strategy formulation.</p>
<h3 id="what-is-user-insight">What is User Insight?</h3>
<p>User insight is a deep understanding of the target users, covering their basic profiles (age, gender, region, occupation, etc.), behavior habits, interests and preferences, purchasing motivations, and barriers. It is obtained through data analysis (website behavior data, social interaction data, CRM data, etc.), user interviews, surveys, and market research, providing a comprehensive and multidimensional user perspective.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>A Practical Guide to Efficiently Managing Images in Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:31:21 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/manage-images-in-obsidian/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When taking notes in Obsidian, using images is almost inevitable. Copying and pasting images directly is indeed convenient, but over time you&rsquo;ll find that the images are chaotically placed, resizing them is troublesome, and centering an image is even more difficult. Another pitfall is that when you delete an image from a note, the file doesn’t actually disappear but remains hidden in the root directory.</p>
<h2 id="what-exactly-are-images-in-obsidian">What Exactly Are Images in Obsidian?</h2>
<p>When it comes to images, many people’s first thought is that &ldquo;inserting an image means adding an image directly.&rdquo; However, in Obsidian, images are more like references to &ldquo;external files.&rdquo; In other words, the images aren’t directly embedded in the note content but are stored in folders on your computer and then displayed in the notes through links or references.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Complete Guide to Installing and Getting Started with Obsidian</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:13:58 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-install-obsidian/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In the era of information overload, more and more people are realizing that organizing and consolidating knowledge is more important than acquiring it. <a href="https://obsidian.md/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Obsidian</a>, a note-taking app focused on <strong>local knowledge management</strong>, has rapidly gained popularity among productivity enthusiasts and knowledge workers in recent years. It is not just another cloud-based note-taking tool but a &ldquo;second brain&rdquo; system that emphasizes <strong>local storage, Markdown formatting, and linked thinking</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="the-core-philosophy-of-obsidian">The Core Philosophy of Obsidian</h2>
<p>At its core, Obsidian is about building a knowledge network that you control. Unlike traditional linear note-taking, Obsidian advocates for <strong>nonlinear linked notes</strong>. By linking different notes, you can create a multidimensional, interconnected knowledge graph.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>