<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:10:48 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Understand Tacit Knowledge in One Article</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/tacit-knowledge/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:10:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/tacit-knowledge/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Tacit Knowledge? Tacit knowledge, also known as implicit knowledge, is a type of knowledge that is difficult to formalize and personal, usually based on experience, intuition, and perception. Unlike explicit knowledge, tacit knowledge is difficult to convey through words, data, or formulas. It is often deeply embedded in an individual&rsquo;s behavior, skills, or culture, and relies on practice and personal experience to acquire.
For example, learning to ride a bicycle is a typical example of tacit knowledge.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Best AdWords Reports: The Ultimate Guide to Boosting Your Ads Performance</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:11:07 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are AdWords reports? The core of advertising optimization lies in data-driven decision-making, and Google AdWords (now known as Google Ads) reports are the key tools to achieve this goal. With AdWords reports, advertisers can gain in-depth insights into the performance of their campaigns and find areas that need to be optimized to maximize the effectiveness and return on investment (ROI) of their ads.
AdWords reports are data reports generated by the Google Ads platform that can display various key data of the campaign in detail, including impressions, click-through rate, conversion rate, cost, etc.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Guide to Search Engine Positioning Software</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:11:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Search Engine Positioning Software Search Engine Positioning Software is a tool that helps website managers, marketers, and SEO experts track and optimize website rankings on search engine results pages (SERPs). It helps companies improve website visibility in a competitive market by monitoring keyword ranking changes, analyzing competitor website performance, and providing improvement suggestions.
In SEO (search engine optimization), search engine positioning software plays a vital role. The goal of SEO is to improve the natural ranking of a website in search engines by optimizing its content and structure.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Improve CTR &amp; CVR: Master the Essential Skills of SEM Copy</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is SEM copy? SEM (search engine marketing) copy is text content created specifically for online advertising, designed to attract users to click and increase conversion rates. SEM copywriting should not only attract attention, but also be practical, able to guide potential users to take action, and directly affect the effectiveness and ROI of advertising.
Understand the composition of SEM ad copy: three main elements    Title: The part that users see at first glance in the search results.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to use Midjourney CREF</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-cref/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 14:56:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-cref/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[&mdash;cref command stands for &ldquo;Character Reference&rdquo;. It is mainly used to extract character features from reference images and apply them to new images to achieve coherence and consistency in character design. It allows users to specify one or more images as content references. Midjourney will use these reference images to help generate images with similar content. This feature is more suitable for anime or games.
Applicable version Midjourney V6 and Niji V6]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Create a Workflow in Coze</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-a-workflow-in-coze/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:34:36 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-a-workflow-in-coze/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is a workflow? A workflow is a set of predefined, standardized steps that can be used to complete a specific task. A workflow contains multiple nodes, each of which completes a fixed task.
To give an example that is not very appropriate but easy to understand, we are all familiar with the brain teaser &ldquo;How many steps does it take to put an elephant in the refrigerator?&rdquo; The answer is three steps: open the refrigerator, put the elephant in, and close the refrigerator.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Use Midjourney SREF to Control Style Consistency</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-sref/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:02:02 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-sref/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The full name of the &mdash;sref command is &ldquo;Style References,&rdquo; which aims to help users replicate and maintain consistency in the style of images.Its main function is to allow users to upload one or more images as style references to guide Midjourney in generating images that are consistent in style with these reference images.This instruction is particularly useful when you come across an image you really like and want to try generating similar or identical styles, but you don&rsquo;t know what that style is.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Step by step guide - How to Create Bot on Coze</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-bot-on-coze/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 08:03:46 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-bot-on-coze/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Coze? Coze is an AI chatbot and app editorial development platform launched by ByteDance. By integrating several plug-ins, Coze&rsquo;s Bot capabilities are greatly expanded and can be applied to various scenarios, such as chatbot, data analytics, and content collection.
Coze page introduction  After successfully registering and entering Coze, on the homepage, you will first see an assistant bot, which will guide you step by step to understand the features and functions of Coze.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Read a ZST File via Python</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 22:00:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Prerequisites To run this code, you need the pandas, zstandard (zstd), and json libraries. If not already installed, you can install pandas and zstandard using pip:
1  pip install pandas zstandard   json is part of Python&rsquo;s standard library, so no additional installation is needed for it.
Note: The above below assumes the data inside the .zst file is the newline-delimited JSON (NDJSON) format. If your data is in another format (e.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Customer Profiling &amp; Segmentation with Python (Source code)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:49:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The sample data and analysis code used in this article are from Kaggle. However, because the actual running results are different from original author, there are slight differences in the analysis part.
The specific analysis process includes:
 Data Preparation Data Cleaning Data Visualization Data Processing Cluster Analysis Customer Profiling and Segmentation  1. Data Preparation Use the KMeans clustering algorithm to divide the data into K clusters:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11  import numpy as np import pandas as pd import seaborn as sns import matplotlib.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
