<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Analyze Sectors in Stock Market?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-sectors-in-stock-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-sectors-in-stock-market/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Software Infrastructure</strong> is the foundational backbone that powers the modern digital economy and the age of artificial intelligence. The products and services in this sector do not directly face end consumers; instead, they serve as <strong>underlying technology platforms</strong>, supporting everything from enterprise operations and data analytics to advanced AI model training and all digital activities in between.</p>
<p>The Software Infrastructure sector attracts significant attention from capital markets due to its unique <strong>value model</strong>:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Create Infographics with AI?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-infographics-with-ai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:17:26 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-infographics-with-ai/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Infographics</strong> have become a key element for elevating content quality and increasing user engagement. Whether deepening a blog reader’s understanding or boosting the shareability of social media posts, a well-designed infographic can effectively visualize complex ideas, making them more persuasive and professional.</p>
<h2 id="method-1-reusing-existing-infographics">Method 1: Reusing Existing Infographics</h2>
<p>This is the fastest and most intuitive starting method, especially if you already have an idea of the design style you want, or simply want to save time on building a layout from scratch.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze a Cash Flow Statement?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-cash-flow-statement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:39:32 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-cash-flow-statement/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>The <strong>Cash Flow Statement (CFS)</strong> is the <strong>closest to reality</strong> among the three major financial statements. Unlike the income statement (which includes non-cash expenses) and the balance sheet (which is only a snapshot at a point in time), the CFS tracks the <strong>actual cash</strong> flowing in and out of the business over a <strong>specific period</strong>.</p>
<p>The ultimate value of a stock depends on how much <strong>free cash flow</strong> a company can generate throughout its lifecycle. The CFS directly reveals a company’s <strong>financial health</strong>, <strong>liquidity</strong>, and <strong>ability to service its debt</strong>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze an Income Statement?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-an-income-statement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:18:21 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-an-income-statement/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>The income statement (also called the Profit &amp; Loss statement or P&amp;L) is like your <strong>monthly budget report or ledger</strong> that records your <strong>entire year</strong> of income and expenses.</p>
<table>
  <thead>
      <tr>
          <th style="text-align: left">Feature</th>
          <th style="text-align: left">Income Statement</th>
          <th style="text-align: left">Comparison: Balance Sheet</th>
      </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Time dimension</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Over a period of time</strong> (e.g., January 1, 2024 to December 31, 2024).</td>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>At a specific point in time</strong> (e.g., December 31, 2024) as a snapshot of assets.</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>What it measures</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left">Measures the company’s <strong>operating results</strong> over that period (did it make money or lose money?).</td>
          <td style="text-align: left">Measures the company’s <strong>financial position</strong> at a moment (how much it owns, how much it owes).</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: left"><strong>Core question</strong></td>
          <td style="text-align: left">“How much <strong>did we earn</strong> this quarter/year?”</td>
          <td style="text-align: left">“How much am I <strong>worth right now</strong>?”</td>
      </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<h2 id="core-accounting-equation-the-essence-of-profit">Core accounting equation: the essence of profit</h2>
<p>The income statement answers only one question: <strong>After offsetting revenues and expenses, how much is left?</strong></p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze a Balance Sheet?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-balance-sheet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 08:01:45 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-balance-sheet/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>The balance sheet is the foundation for understanding a company’s financial health. Its structure is elegantly designed and must always remain balanced.</p>
<p></p>
<h2 id="definition-and-purpose-of-the-balance-sheet">Definition and Purpose of the Balance Sheet</h2>
<p>The Balance Sheet is one of the three primary financial statements (the other two are the Income Statement and the Cash Flow Statement).<br>
Its uniqueness lies in the fact that it presents the company’s financial position at a <strong>specific point in time</strong> (for example: December 31, 2025).</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read P/E Ratio?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:51:13 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Price-to-Earnings Ratio (P/E Ratio)</strong> is one of the most commonly used metrics for assessing a stock’s valuation. It directly compares a stock’s <strong>price</strong> to the company’s <strong>earnings power</strong>.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><strong>What is it?</strong>
The P/E ratio, simply put, tells you how many dollars you must pay in price for <strong>every $1 of profit</strong> a company earns.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>What does it measure?</strong>
The P/E ratio reflects the market’s <strong>expectations</strong> and <strong>premium</strong> for a company. For example, if a stock has a P/E of <strong>20×</strong>, it means investors are willing to purchase the stock at 20 times the company’s annual earnings.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read Financial Statements of a Company?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 07:54:57 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Financial statements are reports that companies prepare periodically (usually quarterly or annually) to <strong>summarize and report</strong> their business activities and financial performance.</p>
<p>Warren Buffett has referred to financial statements as the <strong>“language of business.”</strong> For investors, managers, and creditors, they are essential tools for understanding a company’s financial health, profitability, and ability to meet its obligations.</p>
<p>There are three core financial statements, and together they provide a complete view of a company from different perspectives:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Introduction to Volume Analysis: Using Volume to Verify the Reliability of Price Movements</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:09:55 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When you open any financial chart, your eyes will undoubtedly be drawn first to the fluctuations in price. However, while most beginners focus on price, they often overlook another critical foundational element on the chart — <strong>volume</strong>.</p>
<p>In professional market analysis, <strong>price</strong> and <strong>volume</strong> are the two core pillars for determining market trends. Price tells us “what has changed,” while volume reveals the “strength behind the move” and the <strong>market consensus</strong>. A price move without the support of volume is like a rumor without factual basis — it can reverse at any time.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read Stocks — A Beginner’s Guide Based on Yahoo Finance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:14:03 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the world of investing! When you first open a stock app or financial website, have you ever felt overwhelmed by the dense numbers, curves, and strange professional abbreviations (such as P/E, Beta, Volume) on the page?</p>
<p>For investment beginners, the first task in understanding a stock is to read that seemingly complicated <strong>stock quote sheet</strong>. Once you grasp the meaning of these data points, you can quickly judge a stock’s current value, market activity, and potential risk.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Cold Start Strategy for a New Product</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cold-start-strategy-for-a-new-product/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:12:45 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cold-start-strategy-for-a-new-product/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever invited YouTube creators to review your product? How effective do you think it was?</p>
<p>If your answer is “It brought short-term traffic, but the conversion and retention rates were poor,” then you’ve likely invested your precious early-stage resources in the wrong target.</p>
<p>During the cold-start phase of a product, resources are scarce, and every decision must be accurate and efficient. Many companies instinctively rely on traditional affiliate marketing, hoping to scale quickly with commissions. However, evidence shows that in many cases this is an <strong>inefficient and noise-filled approach</strong>:</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>