<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Notion SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways:  SEM Trend: From June 2015 to January 2023, Notion&rsquo;s paid traffic demonstrated a consistent increase, peaking at an average of 18,585, indicating sustained growth in SEM efforts that likely enhanced overall market presence. SEM Keyword Strategy: During the period from January 2023 to September 2023, paid traffic surged to 148,906, suggesting a proactive and effective keyword targeting strategy during this phase, followed by a decline to 94,601 by March 2024, reflecting strategic adjustments or market shifts.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Notion SEO Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-seo-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/notion-seo-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways:  SEO Trend: From 2012 to 2019, Notion&rsquo;s organic traffic showed a consistent increase, peaking at an average of 14,774, and continued to grow robustly up to January 2024. SEO Keyword Strategy: As of January 2024, 93.19% of Notion&rsquo;s traffic focused on product-related keywords, underscoring a targeted brand-centric SEO approach. SEO URL Traffic Distribution: In March 2024, Notion&rsquo;s homepage attracted 56.33% of total traffic, emphasizing its pivotal role in their SEO strategy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Monday.com SEO Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-seo-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-seo-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways:  SEO Trend: Organic traffic for Monday.com continued to show robust growth, peaking at an average of 14,774 visits by January 2024. SEO Keyword Strategy: As of January 2024, a significant 93.19% of traffic was focused on product-related keywords, indicating a strong brand-centric approach. SEO URL Traffic Distribution: In March 2024, the homepage alone attracted 56.33% of total traffic, underscoring its crucial role in the overall SEO strategy.  Note: The data used in this article is only for the desktop side in the US market.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Wrike SEO Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/wrike-seo-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/wrike-seo-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Insights into Wrike&rsquo;s evolving SEO strategy, highlighting key trends, effective keywords, and top-performing URLs from 2012 to 2023.
Takeaways  SEO Trend: Despite the highest recorded average traffic of 342,720 from 2022-01 to 2023-11, there was a noticeable decreasing trend in traffic. SEO Keyword Strategy: In 2018.2, &lsquo;Team Collaboration&rsquo; keywords drove 41.09% of total traffic, highlighting a focused thematic approach. SEO URL Traffic Distribution: The URL &lsquo;https://www.wrike.com/vag/' received the highest proportion of traffic at 8.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>ClickUp SEM Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-sem-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-sem-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways  SEM Trend: Traffic increased steadily from 11,400 in early 2017 to a peak of 77,844 in mid-2023, illustrating a successful scaling of SEM efforts over time. SEM Keyword Strategy: The top keyword traffic has been consistently high at 17,296 for the last three periods, reflecting ClickUp&rsquo;s focused and effective keyword targeting. SEM URL Traffic Distribution: Major traffic is concentrated on comparison and feature-specific pages, indicating strategic URL targeting to engage users at crucial decision-making points.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>ClickUp SEO Strategy Analysis (2024)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-seo-strategy-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:04:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/clickup-seo-strategy-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Takeaways  SEO Trend: Over the period from 2012 to 2024, ClickUp&rsquo;s SEO strategy led to a consistent upward trend in organic traffic, with significant milestones such as reaching an average traffic of 37,226 by early 2022 and continuing to grow robustly up to January 2024. SEO Keyword Strategy: As of early 2024, ClickUp concentrated significantly on product-related keywords, with 93.19% of their total traffic derived from these terms, illustrating a strong focus on reinforcing brand identity.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A PPC Competitor Analysis of Monday.com</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:46:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/monday-com-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Brand Introduction Monday.com is a dynamic project management tool designed to simplify the way teams work together. Since its inception in 2012, Monday.com has emerged as a vibrant and innovative player in the SaaS industry, offering solutions that enable businesses to centralize task management, project tracking, and team collaboration in one platform.
What sets Monday.com apart is its highly customizable interface, which allows users from various industries including tech, finance, and creative sectors, to tailor the platform according to their specific project needs and workflows.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Read a ZST File via Python</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 22:00:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Prerequisites To run this code, you need the pandas, zstandard (zstd), and json libraries. If not already installed, you can install pandas and zstandard using pip:
1  pip install pandas zstandard   json is part of Python&rsquo;s standard library, so no additional installation is needed for it.
Note: The above below assumes the data inside the .zst file is the newline-delimited JSON (NDJSON) format. If your data is in another format (e.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Customer Profiling &amp; Segmentation with Python (Source code)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:49:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The sample data and analysis code used in this article are from Kaggle. However, because the actual running results are different from original author, there are slight differences in the analysis part.
The specific analysis process includes:
 Data Preparation Data Cleaning Data Visualization Data Processing Cluster Analysis Customer Profiling and Segmentation  1. Data Preparation Use the KMeans clustering algorithm to divide the data into K clusters:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11  import numpy as np import pandas as pd import seaborn as sns import matplotlib.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>14 Best Mind Mapping Software for Mac in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-mind-mapping-software-for-mac/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 21:49:46 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-mind-mapping-software-for-mac/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The capacity to efficiently organize ideas, thoughts, and tasks is more important than ever in today&rsquo;s fast-paced and increasingly complicated work contexts. With its visual and user-friendly approach to brainstorming, planning, and collaboration, mind mapping applications have become indispensable tools for professionals in a wide range of industries.
There is a mind mapping tool designed specifically for your needs and workflows, whether you operate as a project manager managing complex initiatives, a software developer designing fresh solutions, an educator molding young minds, or a creative professional realizing creative ideas.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
