<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:34:36 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How to Create a Workflow in Coze</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-a-workflow-in-coze/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:34:36 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-a-workflow-in-coze/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is a workflow? A workflow is a set of predefined, standardized steps that can be used to complete a specific task. A workflow contains multiple nodes, each of which completes a fixed task.
To give an example that is not very appropriate but easy to understand, we are all familiar with the brain teaser &ldquo;How many steps does it take to put an elephant in the refrigerator?&rdquo; The answer is three steps: open the refrigerator, put the elephant in, and close the refrigerator.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Use Midjourney SREF to Control Style Consistency</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-sref/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:02:02 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/midjourney-sref/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The full name of the &mdash;sref command is &ldquo;Style References,&rdquo; which aims to help users replicate and maintain consistency in the style of images.Its main function is to allow users to upload one or more images as style references to guide Midjourney in generating images that are consistent in style with these reference images.This instruction is particularly useful when you come across an image you really like and want to try generating similar or identical styles, but you don&rsquo;t know what that style is.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Step by step guide - How to Create Bot on Coze</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-bot-on-coze/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 08:03:46 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-create-bot-on-coze/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Coze? Coze is an AI chatbot and app editorial development platform launched by ByteDance. By integrating several plug-ins, Coze&rsquo;s Bot capabilities are greatly expanded and can be applied to various scenarios, such as chatbot, data analytics, and content collection.
Coze page introduction  After successfully registering and entering Coze, on the homepage, you will first see an assistant bot, which will guide you step by step to understand the features and functions of Coze.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Read a ZST File via Python</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 22:00:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-a-zst-file-python/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Prerequisites To run this code, you need the pandas, zstandard (zstd), and json libraries. If not already installed, you can install pandas and zstandard using pip:
1  pip install pandas zstandard   json is part of Python&rsquo;s standard library, so no additional installation is needed for it.
Note: The above below assumes the data inside the .zst file is the newline-delimited JSON (NDJSON) format. If your data is in another format (e.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Customer Profiling &amp; Segmentation with Python (Source code)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:49:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/customer-profiling-and-segmentation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The sample data and analysis code used in this article are from Kaggle. However, because the actual running results are different from original author, there are slight differences in the analysis part.
The specific analysis process includes:
 Data Preparation Data Cleaning Data Visualization Data Processing Cluster Analysis Customer Profiling and Segmentation  1. Data Preparation Use the KMeans clustering algorithm to divide the data into K clusters:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11  import numpy as np import pandas as pd import seaborn as sns import matplotlib.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>14 Best Mind Mapping Software for Mac in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-mind-mapping-software-for-mac/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 21:49:46 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-mind-mapping-software-for-mac/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The capacity to efficiently organize ideas, thoughts, and tasks is more important than ever in today&rsquo;s fast-paced and increasingly complicated work contexts. With its visual and user-friendly approach to brainstorming, planning, and collaboration, mind mapping applications have become indispensable tools for professionals in a wide range of industries.
There is a mind mapping tool designed specifically for your needs and workflows, whether you operate as a project manager managing complex initiatives, a software developer designing fresh solutions, an educator molding young minds, or a creative professional realizing creative ideas.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>12 Best Read-It-Later App in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-read-it-later-app/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 21:55:59 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-read-it-later-app/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The sheer amount of worthwhile and fascinating stuff available can be debilitating. It feels like there is never enough time to stay on top of everything, from important research papers and compelling podcasts to thought-provoking essays and must-read newsletters.
This is where apps that let you read anything later come in handy, providing a lifesaver for people who are overwhelmed by information. These apps, which are made to store content for later use, not only assist in managing your digital to-do list but also improve your reading experience by including features catered to different requirements and tastes.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>13 Best Habit Tracker App in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/habit-tracker-app/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:49:27 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/habit-tracker-app/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Healthy habits are more important than ever for achieving both personal and professional progress in today&rsquo;s fast-paced world. Selecting the best habit tracker app might be overwhelming due to the large number of options available. There is an app for every type of user, be it a data enthusiast who wants to examine every aspect of your progress, a gamer who wants to add a playful element to work, or someone who wants to make routine creation simple.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>5 Best Text Expansion Tool in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/text-expansion-tool/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:49:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/text-expansion-tool/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In the quest for peak productivity, text expansion tools are the unsung heroes for professionals across the board. By turning shortcuts into fully formed text, these tools save time and reduce tedium, no matter your field. This article dives into the top text expansion tools, customized for various roles, to help you work smarter, not harder.
The best text expansion tools for 2024 at a glance    Free trial time Pricing Supported platform Integration AI feature   TextExpander 30 days Start from $3.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>15 Best Calendar Sharing App in 2024 (Features, Pros, Cons, Pricing)</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-calendar-sharing-app/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:07:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-calendar-sharing-app/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Time management and organization are more important than ever in the fast-paced world we live in today. Choosing the correct calendar sharing tool may greatly simplify your scheduling demands, whether you&rsquo;re a busy professional arranging meetings, a student juggling classes and assignments, a project manager managing teams, or a mom organizing family events.
This post seeks to assist you in choosing the ideal app that fits your lifestyle and increases productivity out of the plethora of possibilities accessible, each meeting distinct functions and needs.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
