<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:51:13 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Read P/E Ratio?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:51:13 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-pe-ratio/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Price-to-Earnings Ratio (P/E Ratio)</strong> is one of the most commonly used metrics for assessing a stock’s valuation. It directly compares a stock’s <strong>price</strong> to the company’s <strong>earnings power</strong>.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><strong>What is it?</strong>
The P/E ratio, simply put, tells you how many dollars you must pay in price for <strong>every $1 of profit</strong> a company earns.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>What does it measure?</strong>
The P/E ratio reflects the market’s <strong>expectations</strong> and <strong>premium</strong> for a company. For example, if a stock has a P/E of <strong>20×</strong>, it means investors are willing to purchase the stock at 20 times the company’s annual earnings.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read Financial Statements of a Company?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 07:54:57 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-financial-statements-of-a-company/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Financial statements are reports that companies prepare periodically (usually quarterly or annually) to <strong>summarize and report</strong> their business activities and financial performance.</p>
<p>Warren Buffett has referred to financial statements as the <strong>“language of business.”</strong> For investors, managers, and creditors, they are essential tools for understanding a company’s financial health, profitability, and ability to meet its obligations.</p>
<p>There are three core financial statements, and together they provide a complete view of a company from different perspectives:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Introduction to Volume Analysis: Using Volume to Verify the Reliability of Price Movements</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:09:55 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/volume-analysis/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When you open any financial chart, your eyes will undoubtedly be drawn first to the fluctuations in price. However, while most beginners focus on price, they often overlook another critical foundational element on the chart — <strong>volume</strong>.</p>
<p>In professional market analysis, <strong>price</strong> and <strong>volume</strong> are the two core pillars for determining market trends. Price tells us “what has changed,” while volume reveals the “strength behind the move” and the <strong>market consensus</strong>. A price move without the support of volume is like a rumor without factual basis — it can reverse at any time.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Read Stocks — A Beginner’s Guide Based on Yahoo Finance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:14:03 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-read-stocks/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the world of investing! When you first open a stock app or financial website, have you ever felt overwhelmed by the dense numbers, curves, and strange professional abbreviations (such as P/E, Beta, Volume) on the page?</p>
<p>For investment beginners, the first task in understanding a stock is to read that seemingly complicated <strong>stock quote sheet</strong>. Once you grasp the meaning of these data points, you can quickly judge a stock’s current value, market activity, and potential risk.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Cold Start Strategy for a New Product</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cold-start-strategy-for-a-new-product/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:12:45 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cold-start-strategy-for-a-new-product/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever invited YouTube creators to review your product? How effective do you think it was?</p>
<p>If your answer is “It brought short-term traffic, but the conversion and retention rates were poor,” then you’ve likely invested your precious early-stage resources in the wrong target.</p>
<p>During the cold-start phase of a product, resources are scarce, and every decision must be accurate and efficient. Many companies instinctively rely on traditional affiliate marketing, hoping to scale quickly with commissions. However, evidence shows that in many cases this is an <strong>inefficient and noise-filled approach</strong>:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Analyze a Stock?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-stock/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:40:34 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-analyze-a-stock/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>First, stock picking rarely outperforms the market; ordinary investors are better off choosing passive investing.<br>
But for those who want to research individual stocks themselves, the entire process can be broken down into the following <strong>6 steps</strong>:</p>
<p></p>
<h2 id="step-1-screening-for-ideas">Step 1: Screening for Ideas</h2>
<p>This is the process of narrowing the research scope so you don’t waste time on companies you’re not interested in. Use stock screeners to filter companies that meet specific criteria (such as revenue growth, profitability, debt levels, etc.).</p>]]></description></item><item><title>The Underlying Logic of Investing: How to Understand Interest Rates and Returns?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/interest-rates-and-returns/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:46:32 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/interest-rates-and-returns/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In finance and investing, <strong>interest rates (Rate)</strong> and <strong>returns (Return)</strong> are two foundational concepts. They form the basis of all asset pricing and performance measurement. Understanding their relationship and differences is the first step toward building a robust investment decision framework.</p>
<p><strong>Essentially:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Interest Rate (Rate):</strong> As the <strong>discount rate</strong>, it determines the <strong>current price of an asset</strong>. It reflects the time value of money and the compensation required for taking on risk.</li>
<li><strong>Return (Return):</strong> As the <strong>rate of gain</strong>, it measures the <strong>actual performance</strong> of an investment. It shows how much value an asset generates over time.</li>
</ul>
<p>The most direct metric for evaluating returns is the <strong>Holding Period Return (HPR)</strong>—the percentage change in an investment’s value over a period. However, HPR only reflects the overall outcome.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Take Physical Products Global?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-take-physical-products-global/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 09:25:20 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-take-physical-products-global/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Blindly pouring money into ads or simply shipping your product overseas often leads to overstock and costly trial-and-error.
Successful global expansion starts by answering three strategic questions: <strong>Why go global? Where to go? And how to sell efficiently?</strong></p>
<h2 id="strategic-preparation">Strategic Preparation</h2>
<h3 id="1-define-the-goal-of-going-global">1. Define the Goal of Going Global</h3>
<p>Going global is not a trend to follow — it’s a <strong>strategic decision</strong> based on your company’s growth stage and external pressures.
Before taking any operational steps, companies must <strong>define and quantify</strong> their globalization objectives. These typically fall into three main categories:</p>]]></description></item><item><title>How to Allocate Online Advertising Budget</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-allocate-online-advertising-budget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:50:07 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-allocate-online-advertising-budget/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>As the person in charge of online advertising for a market, facing the new quarterly KPI targets and advertising budget from your company, you need to ask yourself the following questions:</p>
<ul>
<li>What is the main focus of this quarter’s KPIs? Is it <strong>scaling up</strong>, <strong>improving efficiency</strong>, or <strong>increasing customer value</strong>?</li>
<li>Compared with the previous quarter, what are the main changes in KPIs and market conditions? Which channels are facing a sharp increase in customer acquisition cost (CAC)?</li>
<li>Do you think the KPI target is <strong>achievable with the current budget</strong>? Is the growth logic behind it reasonable?</li>
<li>If you believe there’s a significant gap between targets and resources, how will you use <strong>historical ROI data</strong> to negotiate with leadership for more reasonable goals or resources? (Of course, in most cases, you’ll still have to get it done with limited resources 😉)</li>
<li>Once the <strong>final KPIs</strong> are confirmed, how will you allocate this quarter’s ad budget to ensure the KPIs are met?</li>
</ul>
<p>This article uses “improving customer quality” as an example to share a practical framework for ad budget allocation.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Everyday Review: Natural Language-Driven Cross-App Automation</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/everyday-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 07:42:18 +0800</pubDate><author>Chloe</author><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/everyday-review/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><strong><a href="https://www.everyday.new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Everyday</a></strong> is a personal AI assistant designed to help users complete tasks and multi-step workflows across different applications through simple natural language commands. It aims to boost productivity and allow users to focus on what truly matters.</p>
<p>In short, Everyday is an “all-in-one AI” that turns user intentions into real outcomes—helping you clean up your inbox, organize daily work, and drive progress, so you can focus on higher-value tasks.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>