<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Digital Marketing - Tag - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/digital-marketing/</link>
        <description>Digital Marketing - Tag - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:07:56 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/digital-marketing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Integrate Google Analytics with Hugo Website</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:07:56 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/integrate-google-analytics-with-hugo-website/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[After setting up your personal blog site using Hugo and GitHub Pages, you can integrate Google Analytics to monitor SEO performance and track detailed traffic metrics.
Configuration Steps 1. Log into Google Analytics 4 and Create a New Account Sign in with your Google account on the official website and create a new Google Analytics 4 (GA4) account.
Note: Google has fully transitioned to GA4, and the legacy Google Universal Analytics (UA) is deprecated.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Create Effective Location-Specific Landing Pages? 8 Key Elements</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:02:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/creating-location-specific-landing-pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[According to Google’s algorithm mechanics, the search results you receive on Google vary based on your geographic location (or the geographic preferences implied in your search terms). For businesses with physical local stores or those offering location-specific services, creating landing pages tailored to specific regions is essential. These pages not only help search engine crawlers better retrieve and understand your content but also enable visitors to quickly grasp what products or services are available near their residence.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Evaluate User Quality Across Different Digital Marketing Channels</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 08:56:32 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Is User Quality Assessment Critical? The core competition in digital marketing has shifted from &ldquo;acquiring traffic&rdquo; to &ldquo;screening high-quality users.&rdquo; With rising traffic costs and increasingly complex user behavior, blindly pursuing user quantity leads to resource waste: Low-quality users may generate short-term clicks but fail to deliver long-term returns (e.g., fake clicks, coupon abuse). By evaluating user quality, businesses can precisely identify high-value segments, allocate budgets to conversion-ready users, and avoid ineffective spending.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Cohort vs Non-Cohort in Digital Marketing</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 08:56:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Must We Distinguish Cohort from Non-Cohort? If we compare user behavior analysis to marathon analytics:
 Cohort Analysis tracks the same group of runners throughout the race (e.g., &ldquo;What percentage of users who joined in March completed the marathon?&quot;) Non-Cohort Analysis captures real-time snapshots of all runners (e.g., &ldquo;Current number of participants on the track&rdquo;)  An e-commerce platform made a critical error by using non-cohort analysis to observe a &ldquo;15% increase in click-through rate on the redesigned page&rdquo; and immediately rolled it out globally.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Best Landing Page Layouts with Webform</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Landing page design is an integral part of website optimization and marketing activities. Among all the elements that enhance user interaction, Webform plays a key role. Whether it is collecting potential customer information, obtaining user feedback, or driving sales, the layout and design of Webform directly affect the conversion rate. This article will explore in depth how to create an efficient landing page by optimizing form design and page layout.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Do Google Ads for Business</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 07:57:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction to Google Ads How Google Ads Works Google Ads is an online advertising service that allows advertisers to display ads on Google search results pages, YouTube, and other partner websites through an auction system. When users search for keywords related to ads, Google will decide which ads to display in the search results based on a series of factors such as bids, ad quality, and relevance. The core of this process is keywords, and the keywords selected by advertisers will directly affect the exposure and click-through rate of ads.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>PPC Keyword Analysis Guide</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ppc-keyword-analysis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 07:56:50 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ppc-keyword-analysis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pay-per-click (PPC) advertising has become an important tool for companies to gain traffic and increase conversions. The selection of PPC keywords is directly related to the effectiveness of advertising and the return on investment (ROI). Effective keywords can help ads accurately reach the target audience and ensure that the company&rsquo;s ads stand out when potential customers search for relevant information.
Classification of PPC keywords PPC keywords are specific words or phrases selected by advertisers when using pay-per-click advertising, which directly affects the exposure and conversion rate of ads.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Google Conversion Tracking</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 08:44:22 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Google conversion tracking is a feature provided by Google that tracks key actions taken by users after interacting with ads. Whether it is a purchase after clicking an ad, filling out a form, making a phone call, or downloading an app, Google can capture these user behaviors and quantify them into data. This data can not only help you determine whether your ads are effective, but also clearly know which advertising campaigns are driving business growth.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Best AdWords Reports: The Ultimate Guide to Boosting Your Ads Performance</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:11:07 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-adwords-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are AdWords reports? The core of advertising optimization lies in data-driven decision-making, and Google AdWords (now known as Google Ads) reports are the key tools to achieve this goal. With AdWords reports, advertisers can gain in-depth insights into the performance of their campaigns and find areas that need to be optimized to maximize the effectiveness and return on investment (ROI) of their ads.
AdWords reports are data reports generated by the Google Ads platform that can display various key data of the campaign in detail, including impressions, click-through rate, conversion rate, cost, etc.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Calculate CPC of Keywords</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cpc-of-keywords/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 08:45:12 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cpc-of-keywords/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is CPC? Cost per click (CPC) is an online advertising billing model where advertisers pay based on the number of times a user clicks on their ad. This model is very common in search engine advertising and social media advertising, allowing advertisers to precisely control their budgets and ensure that every penny brings the attention of potential customers.
Imagine that when you enter a keyword into a search engine, multiple ads appear on the results page.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
