<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SEO - Tag - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/seo/</link>
        <description>SEO - Tag - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:02:30 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/seo/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>SEO Audit My Site Using SEMrush</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:02:30 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have been suffering from the index of website pages. I have published new articles, but the number of pages not indexed has increased. So I used SEMrush to audit the website as a whole and made some corrections for specific problems to see if the index situation will improve.
The Site audit function is used. After entering the domain name and setting the number of pages to crawl, wait for about ten minutes and you can get an analysis report: The core logic between several indicators:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Choose a Landing Page Name Generator with SEO Keywords</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:32:08 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In SEO optimization, the visibility and click-through rate of a website depend on multiple factors, and the optimization of domain name and landing page name is a crucial part. Although both are important components of website SEO, their optimization focuses are different. Understanding the difference between the two will help you develop a more accurate SEO strategy for your website, thereby improving rankings and user conversion rates. On this basis, this article provides recommendations for two types of tools: &ldquo;domain name generation tool&rdquo; and &ldquo;page title optimization tool&rdquo;.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Google Conversion Tracking</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 08:44:22 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/google-conversion-tracking/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Google conversion tracking is a feature provided by Google that tracks key actions taken by users after interacting with ads. Whether it is a purchase after clicking an ad, filling out a form, making a phone call, or downloading an app, Google can capture these user behaviors and quantify them into data. This data can not only help you determine whether your ads are effective, but also clearly know which advertising campaigns are driving business growth.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Guide to Search Engine Positioning Software</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:11:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-positioning-software/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Search Engine Positioning Software Search Engine Positioning Software is a tool that helps website managers, marketers, and SEO experts track and optimize website rankings on search engine results pages (SERPs). It helps companies improve website visibility in a competitive market by monitoring keyword ranking changes, analyzing competitor website performance, and providing improvement suggestions.
In SEO (search engine optimization), search engine positioning software plays a vital role. The goal of SEO is to improve the natural ranking of a website in search engines by optimizing its content and structure.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Practical skills for Keyword Research and Targeting</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:36 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is keyword research and targeting The meaning of keyword research Keyword research refers to finding common words or phrases used by users in search engines through systematic analysis and data mining. This process helps websites or brands understand the search habits of potential audiences and identify high-potential keywords related to their business or products.
Keywords are not just single words, they can be phrases, sentences, or even questions. For example, users may search for &ldquo;best coffee machine recommendation&rdquo; or &ldquo;how to choose a coffee machine.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Complete Guide to Dimensions and Metrics in Google Analytics</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/complete-guide-to-dimensions-and-metrics-in-google-analytics/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:44:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/complete-guide-to-dimensions-and-metrics-in-google-analytics/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Google Analytics is an incredibly powerful tool for tracking and analyzing website or app traffic. With its vast array of features and metrics, it can provide invaluable insights into your website or app&rsquo;s performance and user behavior. However, for beginners, it can be a daunting and overwhelming experience to navigate through the various dimensions and metrics available in Google Analytics.
In this complete guide to dimensions and metrics in Google Analytics, we will provide you with a comprehensive understanding of the fundamental concepts you need to know to effectively use Google Analytics.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
