<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SEO on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/tags/seo/</link><description>Recent content in SEO on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:06:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction to Content Engineering: Making Content Smarter and More Usable</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:06:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/content-engineering/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="why-should-we-care-about-content">Why Should We Care About Content?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today’s digital world, we interact with &amp;ldquo;content&amp;rdquo; almost every day. Whether browsing websites, scrolling through short videos, using mobile apps, or chatting with smart assistants, the core of these experiences is various forms of content. In other words, content has become the primary medium through which we communicate, gather information, and make decisions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, despite being ubiquitous, content often faces a common problem: &lt;strong>fragmentation and duplication&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Can SEO and SEM Collaborate to Adapt to AI Max for Search?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:08:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</guid><description>&lt;p>With generative AI fully penetrating the advertising space, Google&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://blog.google/products/ads-commerce/google-ai-max-for-search-campaigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max for Search&lt;/a> is transforming how search marketing operates. Similar automated ad products have also emerged on platforms like Meta and TikTok.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Compared to the traditional keyword-centric approach, AI Max for Search relies more on comprehensive learning from user behavior signals, historical conversion data, and creative assets, with AI autonomously deciding when, to whom, and in what combination to display ads. Simply put, manual control is giving way to &amp;ldquo;signal feeding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;model learning.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>FounderPal Review: AI Marketing Tool Hands-On Experience</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/founderpal-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 11:59:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/founderpal-review/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://founderpal.ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">FounderPal&lt;/a> is an AI-powered marketing platform, somewhat similar to &lt;a href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Swiftbrief&lt;/a>, which we previously reviewed. Its core features include:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>AI Marketing Strategy Generator&lt;/strong>: Users only need to input basic business details, and the AI will generate a comprehensive marketing strategy within minutes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>User Persona Generator&lt;/strong>: Helps users identify and analyze target audiences by creating detailed ideal customer profiles.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Marketing Idea Generator&lt;/strong>: Assists users in brainstorming innovative marketing concepts based on industry trends and business objectives.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="website-strategy">Website Strategy&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="hero-section-messaging">Hero Section Messaging&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/founderpal-review/founderpal-hero-section_hu_90b6ecb0c84fb9bf.png" 
 alt="founderpal-hero-section" 
 width="2940" 
 height="664" 
 />&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hands-On with Swiftbrief: How AI Simplifies SEO Content Creation</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:13:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.swiftbrief.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Swiftbrief&lt;/a> is an AI-powered SEO platform designed to streamline the content creation process. Its core features include:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Automatically generating content outlines based on keyword and topic analysis&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Keyword research and clustering&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Integrating SEO data to improve content quality and performance&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="test-walkthrough">Test Walkthrough&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="sign-up--onboarding">Sign-Up &amp;amp; Onboarding&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>During registration, one minor inconvenience is the requirement to enter your website URL—it&amp;rsquo;s a mandatory field:
&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/swiftbrief-signup_hu_85009832f0c2a446.png" 
 alt="swiftbrief-signup" 
 width="2666" 
 height="329" 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Interestingly, the platform experiments with different onboarding methods, letting users choose their preferred learning style during sign-up:
&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/swiftbrief-review/swiftbrief-tutorial-types_hu_71d06b0c0b2f5970.png" 
 alt="swiftbrief-tutorial-types" 
 width="946" 
 height="339" 
 />&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SEO Audit My Site Using SEMrush</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:02:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have been suffering from the index of website pages. I have published new articles, but the number of pages not indexed has increased. So I used SEMrush to audit the website as a whole and made some corrections for specific problems to see if the index situation will improve.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Site audit function is used. After entering the domain name and setting the number of pages to crawl, wait for about ten minutes and you can get an analysis report:
&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/seo-audit-my-site/semrush-site-audit-report_hu_a6f16604bd1c270a.png" 
 alt="" 
 width="1555" 
 height="314" 
 />&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Choose a Landing Page Name Generator with SEO Keywords</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:32:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/name-generator-for-landing-page-with-seo-keywords/</guid><description>&lt;p>In SEO optimization, the visibility and click-through rate of a website depend on multiple factors, and the optimization of &lt;strong>domain name&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>landing page name&lt;/strong> is a crucial part. Although both are important components of website SEO, their optimization focuses are different. Understanding the difference between the two will help you develop a more accurate SEO strategy for your website, thereby improving rankings and user conversion rates. On this basis, this article provides recommendations for two types of tools: &amp;ldquo;domain name generation tool&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;page title optimization tool&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Keyword Research and Targeting in the AI Era</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-keyword-research-and-targeting">What Is Keyword Research and Targeting?&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="keyword-research-understanding-how-users-search">Keyword Research: Understanding How Users Search&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Keyword research refers to analyzing data to identify the words or phrases users commonly use in search engines. These keywords are often not just single words but &lt;strong>search phrases with clear intent&lt;/strong>, such as:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>“Best coffee machine for small apartments”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“High value laptops in 2025”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“Which baby stroller brand is good”&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Through keyword research, we can understand what potential users truly care about, their preferences, and how they express themselves, allowing us to create content that better fits their search habits. Good keyword research makes content more aligned with real searches and improves its chances of being recommended by search engines.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Complete Guide to Dimensions and Metrics in Google Analytics</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/complete-guide-to-dimensions-and-metrics-in-google-analytics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:44:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/complete-guide-to-dimensions-and-metrics-in-google-analytics/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/assets/google-analytics-4.jpg" 
 alt="" 
 
 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Google Analytics is an incredibly powerful tool for tracking and analyzing website or app traffic. With its vast array of features and metrics, it can provide invaluable insights into your website or app&amp;rsquo;s performance and user behavior. However, for beginners, it can be a daunting and overwhelming experience to navigate through the various dimensions and metrics available in Google Analytics.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this complete guide to dimensions and metrics in Google Analytics, we will provide you with a comprehensive understanding of the fundamental concepts you need to know to effectively use Google Analytics. We will cover what dimensions and metrics are, how they work, and the various types of dimensions and metrics available in Google Analytics. We will also explain the differences between dimensions and metrics and how you can use them together to gain a complete understanding of your website or app&amp;rsquo;s traffic and user behavior.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>