<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SEM on Chloevolution</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SEM on Chloevolution</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Landing Page Layouts with Webform</title>
      <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Landing page design is an integral part of website optimization and marketing activities. Among all the elements that enhance user interaction, Webform plays a key role. Whether it is collecting potential customer information, obtaining user feedback, or driving sales, the layout and design of Webform directly affect the conversion rate. This article will explore in depth how to create an efficient landing page by optimizing form design and page layout.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Reduce Search Engine Marketing Cost</title>
      <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-marketing-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 08:44:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-marketing-cost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Search Engine Marketing (SEM) is an effective strategy for promoting products or services to potential customers through search engines. The core of SEM is to increase the visibility of brands in search engines through various strategies and tools, thereby attracting more traffic and potential customers. Imagine that your target audience is searching for information related to your products or services online, and your brand happens to appear at the top of the search results, which will undoubtedly greatly increase the chances of users clicking on your website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical skills for Keyword Research and Targeting</title>
      <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-keyword-research-and-targeting&#34;&gt;What is keyword research and targeting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-meaning-of-keyword-research&#34;&gt;The meaning of keyword research&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keyword research refers to finding common words or phrases used by users in search engines through systematic analysis and data mining. This process helps websites or brands understand the search habits of potential audiences and identify high-potential keywords related to their business or products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keywords are not just single words, they can be phrases, sentences, or even questions. For example, users may search for &amp;ldquo;best coffee machine recommendation&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;how to choose a coffee machine.&amp;rdquo; By studying these search phrases, we can understand user needs and create content that matches them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve CTR &amp; CVR: Master the Essential Skills of SEM Copy</title>
      <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-sem-copy&#34;&gt;What is SEM copy?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SEM (search engine marketing) copy is text content created specifically for online advertising, designed to attract users to click and increase conversion rates. SEM copywriting should not only attract attention, but also be practical, able to guide potential users to take action, and directly affect the effectiveness and ROI of advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;understand-the-composition-of-sem-ad-copy-three-main-elements&#34;&gt;Understand the composition of SEM ad copy: three main elements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/sem-ad-format_hu_ded4b6c4c95f87c7.png&#34; &#xA;       alt=&#34;&#34; &#xA;       width=&#34;1187&#34; &#xA;       height=&#34;108&#34; &#xA;        /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title&lt;/strong&gt;: The part that users see at first glance in the search results. A striking title can effectively attract users&amp;rsquo; attention and stimulate their desire to click.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title>
      <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://chloevolution.com/assets/google-ads-specialist.webp&#34; &#xA;       alt=&#34;&#34; &#xA;       &#xA;       &#xA;       /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising. I have pushed new products, been in charge of high net worth products, experienced the whole account being blocked, and recently started to learn to recruit competent subordinates. Although the market situation is not optimistic in these years, from my personal experience, from the perspective of salary and market demand, overseas advertising specialist is still a good career choice. I hope this article can provide some reference for those who are interested in the position of Google Ads specialist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
