<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SEM on Chloevolution</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/</link><description>Recent content in SEM on Chloevolution</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:12:39 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to SEM Data Analysis</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-analytics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:12:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-analytics/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-sem-analysis">What is SEM Analysis?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-analytics/sem-dashboard_hu_58ca5642b653a6aa.png" 
 alt="sem-dashboard" 
 width="1536" 
 height="409" 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the battleground of Search Engine Marketing (SEM), running ads is only half the battle. What truly sets you apart and even helps you surpass competitors is &lt;strong>SEM analysis&lt;/strong>. It acts as the &amp;ldquo;eyes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;brain&amp;rdquo; of your ad strategy, helping you understand what happened, why it happened, and what you should do next.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simply put, &lt;strong>SEM analysis is the systematic process of collecting, measuring, analyzing, and reporting data related to search engine marketing.&lt;/strong> This data includes, but is not limited to: how many times your ads were seen (&lt;strong>impressions&lt;/strong>), how many times they were clicked (&lt;strong>clicks&lt;/strong>), how many conversions they generated (&lt;strong>conversions&lt;/strong>), and how much you paid for them (&lt;strong>ad spend&lt;/strong>). By digging deep into this data, you can comprehensively evaluate ad campaign performance, identify potential optimization opportunities, and provide solid data support for future marketing strategies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to SEM Bidding Strategies</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-bidding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:04:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-bidding/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-sem-bidding">What is SEM Bidding?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re in a bustling digital marketplace, eager to sell your products or services. Customers are looking for specific items, and both you and your competitors want to display your offerings in the most prominent spots. In this market, whoever gets seen first captures the opportunity. In the world of Search Engine Marketing (SEM), this process of &amp;ldquo;contesting for prominent positions&amp;rdquo; is called &lt;strong>SEM Bidding&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simply put, &lt;strong>SEM bidding refers to the process where advertisers set bids for specific keywords on search engine advertising platforms (like Google Ads, Microsoft Ads) to compete for ad display positions and clicks.&lt;/strong> Your bid, along with other factors like ad quality, collectively determines whether your ad appears at the top when a user searches, or if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear at all.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to Landing Page Optimization</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/landing-page-optimization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:34:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/landing-page-optimization/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="whats-a-landing-page">What&amp;rsquo;s a Landing Page?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When you meticulously plan and launch an SEM ad, successfully attracting user clicks—&lt;strong>where do they go next?&lt;/strong> They don&amp;rsquo;t randomly jump to just any page, nor do they land on your website&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;About Us&amp;rdquo; or blog posts. Instead, they&amp;rsquo;re directed to a carefully considered, specially designed digital &amp;ldquo;gateway&amp;rdquo;—a &lt;strong>landing page&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Put simply, &lt;strong>a landing page is a web page created specifically for a particular marketing or advertising campaign. Its sole purpose is to guide visitors to complete a specific action (i.e., a &amp;ldquo;conversion&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/strong>. This action could be signing up for a newsletter, downloading an e-book, requesting a free trial, purchasing a product, or filling out a contact form, among others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is SEM? A Beginner's Guide</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-basics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:23:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/sem-basics/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-sem">What is SEM?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever searched on search engines like Google or Bing, you&amp;rsquo;ve definitely seen links with &lt;strong>&amp;ldquo;Ad&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong> or &lt;strong>&amp;ldquo;Sponsored&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong> labels appearing above the organic results. These paid advertisements are the core of &lt;strong>Search Engine Marketing (SEM)&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simply put, SEM is a digital marketing strategy that gains traffic and visibility on search engine results pages (SERPs) through &lt;strong>paid methods&lt;/strong>. Its ultimate goal is to increase your website&amp;rsquo;s exposure on search engines, thereby attracting more potential customers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to Paid Search Advertising (PPC)</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/paid-search/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:36:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/paid-search/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-paid-search-advertising-ppc">What is Paid Search Advertising (PPC)?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the world of digital marketing, if you want to quickly gain search engine attention, &lt;strong>Paid Search Advertising&lt;/strong> is definitely your preferred strategy. It&amp;rsquo;s often called &lt;strong>PPC (Pay-Per-Click)&lt;/strong> advertising because, as the name suggests, you only pay when someone clicks on your ad.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simply put, paid search advertising is a way to attract website traffic and potential customers by &lt;strong>purchasing ad placements on search engine results pages (SERPs)&lt;/strong>. These ads appear in prominent positions in user search results, in the form of text, shopping listings, or videos, usually with a clear &amp;ldquo;Ad&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Sponsored&amp;rdquo; label.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Using AI Max for Ad Copy? Beware of These 2 Key Risks</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-ad-creative-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:43:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-ad-creative-insights/</guid><description>&lt;p>In a previous article, we explored how &lt;a href="https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-search-keyword-insights/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max&amp;rsquo;s keyword matching works&lt;/a> and found that it&amp;rsquo;s independently opening up new traffic channels. But AI Max’s capabilities go far beyond that; it can also automatically generate ad copy and headlines.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So, the question is: Where do these automatically-generated creatives come from? And while they offer convenience, what risks are hidden within?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="types-and-frequency-of-ai-generated-creatives">Types and Frequency of AI-Generated Creatives&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>AI Max primarily generates two types of creatives: &lt;strong>titles&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>descriptions&lt;/strong>. In my test account, AI-generated creatives were mostly titles, making up as much as &lt;strong>80%&lt;/strong> of the total.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>AI Max vs. Manual: Who Wins at Keyword Matching?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-search-keyword-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:42:40 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-search-keyword-insights/</guid><description>&lt;p>AI is becoming increasingly important in the advertising world, and &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://blog.google/products/ads-commerce/google-ai-max-for-search-campaigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max for Search&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> from Google is a perfect example. Its core concept is simple: you provide some basic information, and the AI finds the most relevant users, automating your ad campaigns. For advertisers, this sounds very convenient.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But a question quickly arises: how exactly does this powerful AI work? Its internal decision-making process is invisible to us. We know what we put in and what comes out, but everything in between is like a &amp;ldquo;black box.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate and Improve AI Max Performance</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:55:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-to-evaluate-and-improve-ai-max-performance/</guid><description>&lt;p>In Google Ads, AI Max is not a separate campaign type but a set of AI enhancements embedded within existing search ads. As a result, the methods for viewing data and analyzing performance are integrated into your Search campaign reports.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once AI Max is enabled, advertisers are most concerned with performance: how do features like expanded keyword matching, automatically generated ad copy, and AI-selected landing pages impact traffic and conversions? In Google Ads, we can use several key reports to gain deeper insights into AI Max performance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is Google AI Max for Search?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-is-google-ai-max/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:10:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-is-google-ai-max/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you’re running search ads, you’re probably familiar with this scenario: you open Google Ads in the morning, and your account is full of keywords to optimize. Some keywords have spent a lot but brought no conversions, while some long-tail searches you never thought of are showing up in the reports. You spend half a day adding and excluding keywords, yet it feels like you can never keep up with changing search behavior.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Can SEO and SEM Collaborate to Adapt to AI Max for Search?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:08:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/ai-max-for-search-seo-sem-collaboration-customer-acquisition/</guid><description>&lt;p>With generative AI fully penetrating the advertising space, Google&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://blog.google/products/ads-commerce/google-ai-max-for-search-campaigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">AI Max for Search&lt;/a> is transforming how search marketing operates. Similar automated ad products have also emerged on platforms like Meta and TikTok.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Compared to the traditional keyword-centric approach, AI Max for Search relies more on comprehensive learning from user behavior signals, historical conversion data, and creative assets, with AI autonomously deciding when, to whom, and in what combination to display ads. Simply put, manual control is giving way to &amp;ldquo;signal feeding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;model learning.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When to Use Performance Max vs. Demand Gen?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:36:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/demand-gen-vs-performance-max/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="whats-the-difference-between-performance-max-and-demand-gen-campaigns">What’s the Difference Between Performance Max and Demand Gen Campaigns?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Performance Max (PMax)&lt;/strong> is a fully automated campaign type by Google that allows advertisers to run a single campaign across all Google-owned channels—Search, Display, YouTube, Gmail, Discover, Maps, and more. It serves as a &lt;strong>complement to Search Ads&lt;/strong>, helping advertisers reach more potential customers across multiple touchpoints.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Demand Gen Campaigns&lt;/strong>, on the other hand, are designed for visually engaging platforms like YouTube and Google Discover. They focus on &lt;strong>sparking interest and creating demand&lt;/strong> through short-form videos and in-feed content—ideal for attracting new audiences to your brand or products.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Do Tariffs Affect PPC Advertising?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 09:39:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/how-will-the-tariffs-impact-ppc-campaigns/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>The answer is definitely: Yes.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When new tariffs are imposed or existing ones are expanded, the &lt;strong>fundamental cost structure of goods&lt;/strong> changes, and companies&amp;rsquo; bidding behaviors also shift:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Some companies will increase their bids to secure the best ad positions, hoping to maintain existing profits.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Some companies will maintain their current bid levels in the short term, but ad spend may still rise (influenced by other advertisers increasing their bids, leading to an overall industry CPC increase). In the short term, they&amp;rsquo;ll choose to absorb costs to maintain market share.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Other companies will choose to exit this new round of competition, shifting their marketing budgets to other channels.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="what-are-tariffs">What are Tariffs?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A tariff (Customs Duty) is a mandatory tax levied by a sovereign nation or economic entity on &lt;strong>imported goods&lt;/strong> as they cross its customs border. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most common forms of trade barriers in international trade, enforced and collected by customs agencies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Comprehensive Guide to Digital Advertising Types</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/types-of-digital-advertising/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 07:49:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/types-of-digital-advertising/</guid><description>&lt;p>Digital advertising reaches target audiences through diverse formats. This article introduces 11 mainstream advertising types using the &lt;strong>Definition→Targeting Methods→Format Breakdown→Main Platforms&lt;/strong> structure.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-search-ads">1. Search Ads&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Search ads are text or dynamic ads triggered by user search keywords on search engines (e.g., Google, Bing), typically appearing at the top, bottom, or sidebar of search engine results pages (SERPs). Their core logic is &lt;strong>capturing active search intent&lt;/strong> by matching keywords to deliver relevant ads.&lt;br>
&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/types-of-digital-advertising/search-ads-example_hu_7f47d903dd3e1cd8.png" 
 alt="search-ads-example" 
 width="941" 
 height="322" 
 />&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Best Landing Page Layouts with Webform</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 08:34:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/best-landing-page-layouts-with-webform/</guid><description>&lt;p>Landing page design is an integral part of website optimization and marketing activities. Among all the elements that enhance user interaction, Webform plays a key role. Whether it is collecting potential customer information, obtaining user feedback, or driving sales, the layout and design of Webform directly affect the conversion rate. This article will explore in depth how to create an efficient landing page by optimizing form design and page layout.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SEM Advertising: Self-Managed vs. Hiring an Agency – How to Choose?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-marketing-cost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 08:44:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/search-engine-marketing-cost/</guid><description>&lt;p>Are your &lt;strong>SEM advertising costs&lt;/strong> being spent wisely? Most businesses invest budgets in Search Engine Marketing (SEM) without truly knowing where their money goes, or even doubting if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the value. Imagine your target audience searching for information related to your products or services online, and your brand appears prominently in the search results – this would undoubtedly significantly increase the chances of users clicking on your website.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>SEM primarily operates through search engine advertising platforms, such as &lt;a href="https://chloevolution.com/zh-cn/posts/how-to-do-google-ads-for-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Google Ads&lt;/a> or &lt;a href="https://ads.microsoft.com/locale/en-us/microsoft-advertising" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Microsoft Advertising&lt;/a>. Businesses bid on specific keywords to ensure their ads are displayed in relevant searches. When users search for these keywords, they see the ads you&amp;rsquo;ve bid on.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Keyword Research and Targeting in the AI Era</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-keyword-research-and-targeting">What is Keyword Research and Targeting?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Through keyword research, we can understand what potential users truly care about, their preferences, and their ways of expression, thereby creating content that better aligns with their search habits. Good keyword research makes content more relevant to actual searches, increasing the chances of being recommended by search engines, and &lt;strong>is crucial for both improving organic rankings (SEO) and optimizing &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=https://chloevolution.com/zh-cn/posts/sem-basics/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">paid advertising (SEM)&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/posts/keyword-research-and-targeting/keyword-research-targeting_hu_b2db81460d12f062.png" 
 alt="keyword-research-targeting" 
 width="1536" 
 height="409" 
 />&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Write SEM Copy That Converts</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-sem-copy">What is SEM Copy?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>SEM (Search Engine Marketing) copy is text content created specifically for online advertising, designed to attract user clicks and increase conversion rates. SEM copy must not only be eye-catching but also practical, capable of guiding potential users to take action, directly impacting ad performance and ROI. &lt;strong>For a more comprehensive understanding of the components of paid search advertising, refer to &lt;a href="https://chloevolution.com/zh-cn/posts/paid-search/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer "> &amp;ldquo;Paid Search Advertising: An Introductory Guide&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title><link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://chloevolution.com/assets/google-ads-specialist.webp" 
 alt="" 
 
 
 />&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="background">Background&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising. I have pushed new products, been in charge of high net worth products, experienced the whole account being blocked, and recently started to learn to recruit competent subordinates. Although the market situation is not optimistic in these years, from my personal experience, from the perspective of salary and market demand, overseas advertising specialist is still a good career choice. I hope this article can provide some reference for those who are interested in the position of Google Ads specialist.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>