<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SEM - Category - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/</link>
        <description>SEM - Category - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/sem/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Improve CTR &amp; CVR: Master the Essential Skills of SEM Copy</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:44:36 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/create-sem-copy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is SEM copy? SEM (search engine marketing) copy is text content created specifically for online advertising, designed to attract users to click and increase conversion rates. SEM copywriting should not only attract attention, but also be practical, able to guide potential users to take action, and directly affect the effectiveness and ROI of advertising.
Understand the composition of SEM ad copy: three main elements    Title: The part that users see at first glance in the search results.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What does a Google Ads Specialist do?</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:39:15 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/what-does-a-google-ads-specialist-do/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A Google Ads Specialist is a professional who specializes in creating, managing, and optimizing digital advertising campaigns on the Google Ads platform. Specialists are responsible for creating effective campaigns that meet the specific needs of their clients. They must develop strategies to drive traffic to websites, increase brand awareness, and generate leads and sales.
Background After graduation, I entered an Internet company responsible for overseas promotion, and after a year, I switched to be an overseas advertising specialist, and since then, I have started my road of Google advertising.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
