<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Digital Marketing - Category - Chloevolution</title>
        <link>https://chloevolution.com/categories/digital-marketing/</link>
        <description>Digital Marketing - Category - Chloevolution</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 08:56:32 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloevolution.com/categories/digital-marketing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How to Evaluate User Quality Across Different Digital Marketing Channels</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 08:56:32 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/user-quality-assessment-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Is User Quality Assessment Critical? The core competition in digital marketing has shifted from &ldquo;acquiring traffic&rdquo; to &ldquo;screening high-quality users.&rdquo; With rising traffic costs and increasingly complex user behavior, blindly pursuing user quantity leads to resource waste: Low-quality users may generate short-term clicks but fail to deliver long-term returns (e.g., fake clicks, coupon abuse). By evaluating user quality, businesses can precisely identify high-value segments, allocate budgets to conversion-ready users, and avoid ineffective spending.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Cohort vs Non-Cohort in Digital Marketing</title>
    <link>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 08:56:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Chloe</author>
    <guid>https://chloevolution.com/posts/cohort-vs-non-cohort-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Must We Distinguish Cohort from Non-Cohort? If we compare user behavior analysis to marathon analytics:
 Cohort Analysis tracks the same group of runners throughout the race (e.g., &ldquo;What percentage of users who joined in March completed the marathon?&quot;) Non-Cohort Analysis captures real-time snapshots of all runners (e.g., &ldquo;Current number of participants on the track&rdquo;)  An e-commerce platform made a critical error by using non-cohort analysis to observe a &ldquo;15% increase in click-through rate on the redesigned page&rdquo; and immediately rolled it out globally.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
